Your armors have already been upgraded, um, so like you already have the new armor technically.
Did it change the healing things or is everything still the same?
You have two instead of one.
Two instead of one, yes.
Okay.
Something that I could like adjust technically but not have to adjust.
Gotcha.
Okay, yeah.
What's good?
That's the music for right now.
I think I want to do some shopping.
I could be down for, so I think on the list right now, just like if today's the day of just like putzing and taking care of things before we start our next Lycan thing, I'm fine with trying to visit like some spots to buy a few things.
We've got, I've got about a thousand coins.
I'm assuming everybody's got about that.
I got a lot of money.
We didn't get our partial gold yet.
We didn't get our partial gold.
That's a good point.
You guys just didn't add it.
So it'd be, if you take the tokens, I think you only get 25 gold.
because this is not betting on the side, but your new raise, you would have gotten 45.
45 gold?
How did I get the rest of this gold, then, if we're all betting that much?
We got a shit ton from the fighting pits.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Remember, Grandpa Bot really played it up.
I was going to say, I've got 1,082 right now, just in my purse.
I have, like, 850.
And I got some platinum.
There you go.
I'm counting nothing but gold.
Oh, no, I got silver, never mind.
You said 45, right, Jonathan?
What kind of access, you said we have better access now, what kind of access do we have in the library?
Would I be able to peruse generally known low-level evocation spells?
Would you guys like to go to your new, like, room area?
Let's go, let's take our shit to our new room.
Yeah, let's go and check it out.
Move all your shit.
Get your fucking snacks out of here.
God.
A big...
I'll describe it in detail, but as you guys... Yeah, there's your hero.
You, um... You make your way to this new fort the Omen Knights possess on their own.
Um...
You walk in, you see this large sort of slate gray room.
It's not as circular as I've got it drawn in.
It's more like octagonal with sharp edges that are just making up a lot.
So it's got edges to it.
You notice there are 10 doors other than the entry door that you walk into.
In the hallway, there's some stuff you didn't really look into.
But as you walk in, you see this open space of multiple, like,
tables for eating there's like its own little cafe area some fighting dummies weapons things like that and you notice that there are like various overnight sort of practicing and moving around particularly there seems to be like a large group around the first fighting pit doing something but the big thing to go to the questions you guys just asked is you remember that when you were looking in the library that like there was like this like arcane projection
Right here, there is a sort of inset to the wall arcane projection that's got like a bunch of different things.
Like it almost just looks like a home screen for a computer.
Like it has different things that it can do.
Cool.
Roughly how big is this entire space?
Just like width-wise.
200 feet.
Pretty massive, like football field size.
It is like...
Like, enough that there are roughly what seems to be around 40 people in this space.
You notice, and this would be like an easy history check, and you guys have been in the Legionnaire long enough that you can figure this out, the Omen Knights have 10.
The positions are the squads.
Squadrons.
Okay.
Are there a lot of people we don't recognize?
You don't recognize any of them.
Interesting.
These are people you've never interfaced with.
Okay.
Except for the person at the front door.
You see a guard as you walk into the space.
A man to your guys' right.
Long, luscious hair.
He's got like platinum armor on with like his symbol instead of the normal black one.
But it's Silvera Sunseeker.
Just goes, oh.
Right, because I fucking retired or something.
That's totally true.
Like, this is just a part-time gig.
They sort of like offer me something to come and talk with the new people and then guard the door.
But I mostly work at Sunny Days.
It's the grocery store in the market.
My father owns it.
It's pretty rad.
Well, Sunseeker, that's quite a fall from grace for you.
How do you feel about that, Mr. Ego Man?
well i thought it's the most successful business chain in the market i thought overnight was your um how do i say it uh your personality the last mission i went on my entire family died laser laser and laser were uh were family members of you intentionally get it wrong at
Oh, dear, yes.
They're dead, though.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Cousins of yours?
Friends.
Lifelong friends.
Will be missed, for sure.
Oh, let's part one out.
He pulls it up here.
Starts drinking at the door.
He goes, um, right, so you guys are the new guys.
I forgot about that.
Julie, oh shit, he's always gone.
Oh, he has this thing, soft tissue.
He probably won't make it.
I think they're going to demote him pretty quickly, but I'll have to promote somebody else instead.
Your new commanding officer is, I mean, points at the fighting pit, and he's like, she's putting on a show right now, but you want to report into her when you guys get all settled in.
And then he's got his large spear sort of pointed to the top corner, and he goes, you guys' room is number nine right up there, so
Get comfortable, familiar.
I'm working another 30 minutes.
You guys want to get a beer afterwards.
Good to see you guys.
Good luck at the grocery store.
So do we see any...
Is there, like, an armament area or, like, just, like, extras if you wanted to get... Like, down here.
Okay.
This is just, like, basic weapons and...
Nothing better than what you guys would have in theory.
Maybe, like, a plus one, but not because it's magical just because
Is there a workspace, workshop area with maybe some parts, extra?
Right, right.
there are a couple people there seems to be a rounder more dwarvish origin fella fully bald on top very full beard on the bottom dark tan skin with some brown eyes short for a dwarf his name is a Rurik Flint Forge he's got a little name tag that says that
He goes, hey, how can I help you?
Well, we're just new, and we're checking out the facilities.
Is there anything we should know about your station here?
Yeah, 100%.
You have any weapons that you like or maybe don't particularly like, and you're like, can I do something with this?
I've got a unique smithing style.
It's like I can make it good with a cost, or I can just make it a little bit better up to you guys, but...
You bring weapons to me, a little bit of money, and I'll hook you guys up.
Is this kind of our new ham hock, or is there a difference in what they do?
Are they just plus one-ing the weapon?
This guy can do certain things.
You'd have to go through his list, and I'd have to find my list of what he can do, but in essence, he can take things and give you...
what's called like a deadly edge or something where it's you always roll with disadvantage but when you hit you roll your d20 as the damage die instead so like he can do things to weapons to make them like weird but good and like other things like that i have to find my full list that's cool like a min max type yes you can do things like that too just weapons
Yes, well, he might have some armor stuff.
Hold on, let me, while you guys chat tactically, we'll get back to that.
Also, I dropped off those scales with Hamlock.
Would it be reasonable that she'd be able to make something before we leave the dome or before we're done with the next mission?
Yeah, like you wouldn't, you'd like to get like a shoulder thing or a breastplate.
Just to update the, I guess I'm on half plate, so he gets like one chestplate, one shoulder thing.
Yes, that would be something you can get done like the next day or so.
Okay, cool.
She's already got the dragon scales.
We rested in the cave and we walked back since like morning.
Late morning, yeah.
Okay, so we had the whole day.
Yeah, I'm good.
I'm okay visiting like a market area.
I was going to say, I wanted to look at the screen and just kind of flip through.
Maybe see what... Yeah, Altered Self.
Altered Self is a second level icon off that screen.
That'd be fine.
Yeah, or I guess is it more a directory?
Or is it like a repository of the actual spells?
What did we say?
50 gold per level?
What's the fee for copy?
Okay, so talking with Rurik, he tells you, he's like, I can make it precise.
I can make it brutal.
I can make it aggressive, balanced, surgical, destructive, calculated, vicious.
He's like, you're writing this down.
Just kidding.
You don't have to.
I got it.
Masterwork or perfect the edge.
Up to you guys.
And with each of those, we just further inquire and learn.
You learn about what?
There's four ways.
could also just tell you but only if i'm interested in trying to do something mild to light bringer but i don't think i want to do like the first one you described where it's like disadvantage all or nothing yeah so uh precise the first one is weapon critical hits on 19 and 20 does not stack with improved critical the class bonus brutal is after rolling your damage dice roll uh roll a second die of the same type if it is the same as your damage die your damage becomes the max possible so
So you roll a d10, you roll an 8, you throw another d10, it's another 8, you roll max damage instead.
There's a chance of buffing it to max.
But I have to match the same number.
Yeah, you roll a 1, you roll a 1, you roll a 10 instead.
Aggressive is reroll ones on the damage die.
Balanced is roll the damage die twice, average the two rolls.
Surgical is when a specific number, your choice,
Calculated is reroll ones and twos on damage die.
Calculated is advantage on damage rolls.
Roll damage twice, take higher of two.
Wait, with Great Open Master?
I already do damage, it's not attack.
It's not attack, it's damage, yeah.
Calculated is advantage on damage rolls.
Roll damage twice, take the higher of two.
Vicious is deal three times the damage on a critical hit.
Modifier is still two times, but the damage is three times.
So...
you're getting way better and better and better and better the price that costs yeah it costs a pretty penny i don't have that master work is improved damage die by one step example a d6 becomes a d8 a d12 becomes 2d6 yeah d12 on a sword swing uh perfected edge is improved damage die by two steps oh coming so what would i roll if i'm a
and then 2d8 instead, so it just bumps it.
And what was the price on those last two?
Perfected Edge is $10,000, Masterwork is $3,000, Vicious is $2,400, Calculated is $1,000, Destructive is $500, Surgical is $250, which is pretty good for that one.
That would be, um... That's only on the web.
...destructive.
That was the one that's 1,000.
Sorry, the 500 one.
Do we... Do we have a... Just open to the public, or I guess open to us...
Great, I'll just ask about the Dragonblade armor.
Yeah, I haven't, uh... You guys were just there.
Just, just.
Yeah, we were in kind of a rush.
Yeah, so if you guys wanted to say while you were there, you were doing something.
That's fine, because he just wants to shop.
Yeah, yeah, I just want to see if we got anything cool.
Um...
Yeah, can I, can I go in and just be like, uh, yeah, can I take a peek at, uh, anything, anything that might be good for me?
You know, not rip my hands, but, you know, we got anything cool?
Hammock looks around, you see, like, in her shop is this huge, um, like, just mess of a bunch of different things.
She goes, uh, what do you want?
I could try to find something.
I don't want you to just be like, hey, find me a list of ten things, and then somebody has to make a list of
It really just seems like you're trying to bypass the restrictions placed on your class so to speak to
She's like, well, I don't have a ring of power right now, but I've got the blueprints and schematics so I can pump in the right arcane enchantments.
It'll take me a little bit.
I can run it on my machine over there.
You see, like you're in, because if you guys remember, you walk into her shop and it's like the main space and then like to the left is her shop.
special shop that normally there's just like her and leopold do stuff in you're in that space with her now and she points over and she's got this arcane bench that has runes all over it glyphs circles things like that and you see she like walks over and she presses some things and she drags over like sliders on the arcanes um and like lights up and you see like these um like um framing sort of rises up out of it like printed and then she's like put
zapping it and turning it and engraving it she's like that'll um take a little bit but it'll turn it out tomorrow uh i'm really focusing on this armor piece over here uh you see that she had just been given the scales for so she's like thinking she's like drawing up like a shoulder pad that goes into like a chest piece like like that'll be ready ring of protections are like uh
Normally pretty pricey, but you guys are kind of... Well, actually, she looks at Leopold.
A thousand gold.
Well, you might take it off that there machine, because I don't have that much money.
Maybe I'll come back later and try it.
Don't you worry.
I might be able to fix something up later.
All right.
We'll try that.
This chump... Really starting to create the divide there.
If I'm not an apprentice, then our relationship is over.
All saving throws?
It's pretty slick.
They're pretty great.
The saving throws is almost better than the armor class, but yes.
Well, it depends on how bad your armor class is.
Ring of Predictions and by the order of normal, you buy 1,000.
Fuck!
But really, it would affect my AC even from there.
Oh, there you go.
Because it's magical, right?
It just stays on?
Yeah, so it'd go from 14 to like 15.
I mean, which isn't nothing, but... Would we...
Have the opportunity, because didn't we burn through...
I wasn't holding any, but I know I used one.
Well, one was given, administered to me, the liquid potions.
Yeah.
Or the syringes that we had.
Oh, right.
What's that look like as far as inventory?
Maybe that's where I'll spend our money.
I had two, and now it shows I have one.
Yeah.
I don't think I have any.
I don't think I have any heals.
Because you got me up twice.
You used my suit, and then I think you used a syringe.
Yeah, well, yeah, because...
Yeah, I've never used a potion, and I've had two this whole time.
And so we used one on you, so I've got one actual physical potion.
I'm probably going to spend my thousand on that rather than a ring.
You know, that's not a bad idea.
No, I can give you $300 or $300 gold, so you can get the ring.
Jonathan, I have a book.
It's called The Chronicles of NNA.
You happen to remember what that is?
New New Arbor.
Ah, okay.
Excellent.
It's on hold.
New New Arbor.
At the library.
Might have to read through that at some point.
Do you want her to finish?
Or you're going to try to make her read?
I mean, I can't right now, but... Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
Do you want her to finish the ring for now, early game?
700 more gold I can spend on potions.
Yeah.
Just so we've got our buffs and sets.
How much gold do you have?
He's got 700 and change.
I got like 750.
Can I like try to convince Hamhawk to give me a little better of a deal?
Can I be like... You guys were talking when you guys wrecked our
Okay, all right.
Okay, yeah, yeah, I'll take that out of my, and I'll have her continue.
So you're gonna buy a...
So only take 250, because I've got 750.
Okay.
And I am now destitute.
You're going to buy health potions?
Yeah, I still have 820 gold for essentially to spend on some potions.
That's about what I have.
I was going to try and...
I was going to spend 100 on a level 2 spell.
I've got 700 worth potions, so I need at least a couple.
I don't know how much materials will be for that sword, but I was going to try and scrounge up stuff and...
Whatever's left, I can buy.
It's already going.
You can tell that she was probably going to give you a better price even, but the fact that you guys did not give her that power core.
Like, just a little penny's just like...
Right.
It's still awesome.
arcane power from time to time and it just like we'll do it for her but um yeah you got you you could have had a better deal but you guys started burning that bridge slowly but surely if we ever just like get the fuck out of here we are taking that with us we're gonna take that whole case thing that can be take it apart put it in the pocket where
Alright, yeah, I'm cool, I'm cool.
You guys gonna go library, or?
Is it, would there be a potion, there's no potion shop, how did we get our syringes?
Like a stop to carry, or?
You, um, you went to a shop downtown.
Oh, did we?
Yeah.
Okay.
In the storm district, we found a couple shops.
What's this dusty old guy, what was his name?
I've got it somewhere.
Uh, yeah, we can look it up.
I do have it.
Oh, the potion guy.
Yeah.
He was a character.
I was going to say, I could pull up the notebook.
So we've got potions, spells, the library.
Is there anything else we want to do today before we start prepping for our... No, if we just need to get any other information about our investigation.
I was going to buy some materials for the laser sword.
Is there anywhere we could sell stuff that we've picked up along the way?
When are these stress points going to come into play?
They already have.
You've got five.
You've already got a... Yeah, you've got an iron arm.
Yeah, well, I mean, that was from touching the thing, though, right?
That wasn't a matter of...
I like to think that Radish is just peeking around the corner watching.
What the fuck?
What are these people doing?
They're not looking out for their son, are they?
No, they're not.
I do think it's hilarious that in a D&D campaign that NPCs, plot-wise, can be injured even though
The party's just like fresh as new.
I couldn't find him.
All I have is Selena.
uh okay so jonathan where should i uh be looking for supplies for my general wear okay sunny days sunny days i will oh so they're not just a grocery store they're also a uh store you're thinking too modern this is still high fantasy so like it's like a general general store okay
I think while these guys are dealing with that, I'll peel off to...
Okay, so this is technically before you had gone to the new building.
Okay.
So we'll say this is like your guys' walk-up.
You guys want to go shopping first.
So we'll say which you want to go to market.
I just have a general city map, so we'll call this the same for all of them.
Is it Nerman?
It was Nerman.
The Feathered Quill, scroll shop located off the side street in Market District.
There's also Philandra Sprawlweaver?
I think it was supposed to be Skrullweaver.
Skrullweaver?
Philandra.
Enigmatic.
She had the Skrull Shop.
Nurman had just like the general store.
I think it just mixed it up a little bit.
Okay.
Who do you guys want to go first?
General store?
Or the scroll shop?
There's only two spots I think we gotta hit.
I think so.
Take care of your stuff first.
Uh, yeah.
Yeah.
These are fantastic, by the way.
Yeah, those are pretty yummy, aren't they?
Have you had the dots?
No.
Okay, so in general they're really good, but that flavor I haven't had before.
It's like a garlicky parmesan.
Yeah, exactly.
Okay, so sunny days it is to visit Sunseeker and his family.
he's probably still on shift oh yeah yeah yeah he's still he because he would be he would technically be um still on guard right on the berries shop trash right there um and i have a shopping list i presume of things that i'm going to want to buy say that you like get the stuff you need okay
her doing a run in the ring.
It was really funny to watch.
So it's just, what, they coming?
Soon.
Okay.
We'll just make the list retro and say that.
You could get all the things you need.
Whatever I need.
You would need metal to make the frame, gems, we'll say gems worth 500 gold, things like that.
Okay.
So 500 gold is what it would send me back Roughly you could say cost of metallic material and like leather for leather wrapping it things like that would be a hundred total and gems diamond worth 500 gems or Equivalent so you could do multiple 600 gold 600 gold call it good Okay
Same as health pots, so 50 for a basic, 250 for a greater.
What's a greater?
Is that a 2d4?
2d4 plus 2 is basic.
What's a greater?
Greater is 4d4 plus 4.
Superior is 6d6 plus 6, and supreme is 10d4 plus 10.
I can do three graders.
That's 250 apiece?
Yes.
250 apiece, and I'll buy one because I have 290 left.
250.
We're going to have to make some money, though.
We've got to do this next mission.
Maybe not take a token.
Yeah.
You guys have been very item and OP driven right now.
100%.
You've got to do it when you're weak.
But you guys, yeah, so you go to the Spoken Quill, you find Nermin, you speak to him, and he's like, oh, sure, we can work on this.
Gets that to you.
You guys will say, so you want two craters, right?
And I'm buying a grader.
Three graders, okay.
Three graders, you're doing material components.
He tells you that he doesn't have the gemstones, but that he says her name, and you're like, he's like, oh, but there's this gal, Philandra.
And you're like, we know Philandra.
So then you go to her place.
She's like the very, she's the elven woman who's just like, oh, darling, of course.
and just like gems inlaid in different spots with like the price points already on them.
Just like take your pick.
Excellent.
Always a pleasure.
Could I have traded my non-magical shield for like a big glove?
like maybe it's like a yes she would also have something like that like a full-length glove yeah you can get a leather one so it's maybe not like sheer velvet or something like that but like you can just pick a leather writing glove or something like that yeah just a full arm just she's like oh this this is an antique from uh back when people were still riding horses i presume but she's like um she looks at it she goes 10
Well, I happen to have this awesome shield.
Sold.
You could tell she was going to list the price no matter what.
I should say yes on that actually.
I give her my little shield.
And then you go to, oh, I guess, do you want to go meet the Sunseeker family or get everything from Nervin?
Sure, I'll go talk to the Sunseekers.
They're all giant haired.
Curious what they'll look like.
Dad and Mom are all just surfer bros. You walk into this very nice, it's like you walk in and the doors go shhhh.
They go outside and it's like a holster.
looking large aisles people like carts moving around there's like regular cashiers and you see a man unmistakably a sun seeker he is 6'7 gorgeous blonde hair other than the lord of advancement maybe the most elven gentleman you've met he's definitely older in age he's moving around but just like he like
very slowly he's not in a rush hands sort of gently clasped behind his back just admiring his store looks to you doesn't recognize you guys but just gentle nods and sort of like could not be bothered just keeps walking he disappears into the aisles and you're like who the fuck is that I'll grab a cart uh start looking down the aisles hold on let me get up
Today we're running a sale on ground chicken.
Clean up on aisle four.
There's no way I did that.
I love that you guys have the spiced cranberry Sprite.
They make a spiced one?
It's good.
It's the holiday Sprite.
Oh damn.
That's great.
You're, you know, a seven-foot warforged with this tiny little carpet.
Looking around for leather, some iron.
You take out this, like, very organized shell.
It's got little prices.
You build everything together.
Sunseeker walks by and he goes, just like, not snotty, but just,
very well I love that for you yes check out our sale in the rotisserie chicken if you wouldn't mind oh and Serge keeps going just can't be bothered chicken it's like Monsters Inc what is this
How much is the chicken on sale for?
Five silver.
I'll also throw one of those in my cart.
This is dazzling background music for getting a haircut in elevators.
A haircut in an elevator?
That's a great description.
Yeah, I'll pick the materials up and rotisserie chicken for the road.
As you're getting checked out in the line.
I thought we've never seen you actually eat food.
Oh no, I just throw it into my metal husk.
It plops out whenever the Steel Defender comes out.
It just starts smelling really bad.
Goes over to that line.
You see a room flash that rings up the price as they're just checking it out.
This little teenage half-elf just goes, anything else?
Do you have any coupons with us?
No, I'm not a frequent shopper here.
No, nothing more.
Have a sunny day, sir.
Well, you as well.
I hate it here.
Well, you can always be a legionnaire like me.
If you work hard.
Do you think I can be a legionnaire?
Oh, sure.
Why don't you sign up for the next recruiting fair?
My mom says I'm anemic.
Well, don't listen to her.
Get on out there.
Oh, yeah.
But you get the things you need, so go ahead and give me, as you've got everything together, that's it right there, go ahead and give me just either, I bet your arcana's better than your intelligence, but either arcana or intelligence check to sort of put together how long it's gonna take you to complete this.
Yeah, yeah, that's plus eight.
Ah, 18, maybe.
26.
Yeah, so that's a plus 8.
You think you can knock this out either with one really long night or two nights of work?
I'm going to do it.
I'm going to pull an all-nighter.
Well, you know, I mean, I'm absorbed into this.
I'm not even going to look up.
I'm just going to set my sights to it.
Does he meditate like I do?
Does he actually require, like, a full...
He has to be inactive for a certain amount of time.
I think it's only six hours for a sentry to rest out.
So he's, like, always on, like, sentry guard.
But it's eight, yeah.
Which is why I have watched... People eat spiders.
Yep, sentry.
Cool, cool, cool.
So we got...
What is this?
Century's Rest.
Six hours inactive for Century's Rest.
No.
I think you touched the beam and you down leveled.
I died?
Took another 20 stress points and evaporated into dust.
How did that happen?
I'm pulling an all-nighter in the pocket workshop.
I think we're back to the place.
Can I look at the arcade store?
there is big sort of fighting exhibition thing going on here you guys know your room is up there there's an arcane screen up here Kaladin is checking out the screen as you walk over to that you walk up and you see that in your omen knight armor towards your wrist on like either a strap or a
you see a rune start to glow that you hadn't seen before.
It's like flashing.
You're like, oh.
Closer it gets, the brighter it gets.
And you close it and it goes... And then the screen flashes and it says, Welcome, Kaladin.
Configuring settings.
Your system's awkward.
As you're looking through, it looks like a personal sort of library-type deal where you can request things to be put on hold.
there's a little tube to the side where like you're playing around with it over the course of like the next 10 minutes or so you're like oh i want to see if i can get this scroll and you press it and it says like normal deposit fee it'll be like you know 10 gold to rent and then you you know transfer the funds and then it comes in and you can scan the scroll and stuff the learnings
So is it just $10 to scan?
$10 to rent and then whatever cost of like normal stuff.
So like your School of Magic is still half price.
All the normal rules apply, but it's cheaper than going to it before and paying.
That's okay.
So I think it's abjuration.
Oh, so if it's within your...
It's half time money.
Cool.
Nice.
How do you look those up?
So you can go manage spells.
Yeah.
It'll take you into your, so if you look at your spell list and hit manage spells, you can look at spell book.
Okay.
Prepared is what you've got.
Spell book is everything in your current book.
Add spells, then it accesses all of the wizarding lists.
But to answer the other question, it's like not even on your character sheet.
It's like the basic class description will tell you that like the class of wizard, the school, you have one of the abilities is like when you transcribe spells of your school, it's half price, half time.
Okay.
So I need to, because it's a level two, I need 50 gold.
I only have 101 gold right now.
I had 96 gold and 50 silver.
Okay.
So you don't have nine gold.
Let me see.
So I can finish the rental.
Could I sell my scimitar to the guy?
I got 37.
I'll send you nine gold.
To the guy?
Yeah.
They'll give you 20 gold for it.
All right.
Yeah, I'll give you that 20.
All right, cool.
I can now pay the 110 total.
Take these off.
To do all of that.
Okay.
To do everything.
So I'm going to copy Alter Self into my spell book.
So I'm going to leave the shield that's here in my inventory so that it keeps affecting my...
I feel like there should be more spells.
So look at that spell.
So then there's level ones.
You're only a level one wizard.
Oh, okay.
So that's...
So that's everything you can currently have access to.
For level one.
Got it.
Okay.
So if I was a higher level wizard, I could...
Correct.
Then there are level twos and threes and fours.
You've got to decide, like, what's the trade-off for 17 Artificer or 16 Artificer?
Like, where do you want to stop an Artificer?
Yeah.
Because that'll dictate how far you're willing to go in Wizardry.
Yeah, well, and that was the other thing.
I think I was going to do another level of Artificer for the next one.
Yeah.
It's going to be a while before I get to those.
Cool.
So I've got to now have zero volts.
You know what?
I might have some higher-level Artificer spells, actually.
Oh, but I can't add.
You just get what you get.
Any other plans?
What is he saying?
The room.
Check out our bedroom.
I think maybe he just said room, but maybe it meant the bedroom.
The cot quarter.
Jonathan, is there any advantage to honing your skills in the fighting pits?
Is that just kind of maybe for flair?
Mostly for flair, but if you did it every single time you made a point to tell me that you're going to go train, eventually you can have a benefit.
If you really, really have a really weak stat, like strength,
Eventually you get a bump here.
Okay, okay.
I had a donut bowl in ages.
It's a churro buggy.
Will our new commanding officer essentially give us the lowdown on the new mission?
Because we've got a very small group.
So I think we just need to decide how close we are to doing that when we leave the room.
Well, let's talk to her first because we probably have to walk past.
We might as well just say hi.
CEO.
You're talking with Sylvaris at this point.
He's like, run along, dude.
Anyway, your new officer, she's actually right there, and he's trying to point between the crowd, but there's a lot of people moving, so you don't know who he's talking about.
But he's like, her name is Leora.
Leora Wagner.
Anyway, pretty hardcore.
You're going to like her.
He's like, I fucking wish Donnie was here.
They used to be old adventuring buddies.
They know each other.
But that's neither here nor there.
Anyway, she'll give you more of a rundown on your case.
She told me to watch out for you guys.
So ride on whenever you're ready.
Start eating, Chip.
Leora?
Leora, yeah.
Leora.
What was the last name?
Wagner.
Wagner?
W-A-G-N-A-A-R.
Okay.
Yeah.
Leora.
L-E-O-R. No known nickname?
Probably Agnar.
Well, y'all have to try that one out.
Yeah, I'm not going to do that.
See ya.
Give it a shot.
So, yeah, let's make our way.
hollering, hooting, cheering.
Some people throwing in, they have like side bets going where they're like betting some of their money just in between each other.
And you see two people fighting in the pit.
The first one is a dwarven woman.
She's got like a thick stubble on her face, shaved half side of her head.
The other half is like wild and long, bushy eyebrows, piercing green eyes.
obvious other heritage very dark skin she's got a nice like shortcut throw it kind of goes fully like nice hairline it's not to the back or anything pretty fair woman live form she's not overly muscular she looks more fascinating very well wrapped fist just like from mid forearm all the way down past her
And then after, like, you hear somebody's, like, ringtone just ding, ding.
And she goes, whew.
Sort of shakes out her hand, starts unwrapping it.
Everybody's, like, patting her on the back.
She's like, all right, all right.
Get back to fucking work.
We got jobs to do.
For Christ's sake.
And she looks and she goes, ah, my new recruits.
Hard to wear my manager.
She, like, wipes some blood off her face.
She's like, shit.
She, like, wipes it on her tattered robe.
She goes, um, I'm Leora.
about the space.
You guys pretty well familiarized.
Sorry, I don't normally do this.
We're pretty chill up here.
You guys, from what I know, made your way up the ranks pretty quickly.
Congrats.
Thank you.
Sorry.
What do you not normally do?
Names.
Introductions.
Not my thing.
I like to be on the streets still.
I'm very much not loving this position where they're mostly political and
Tall one, your name?
Oh, Leopold Magnus, at your service.
She takes a look, she goes, he, she, they, person, non-person, like really looking in your mirror, she goes, huh, haven't seen someone like you?
Oh, well, I do get that a lot, but I can assure you that I'm quite adept.
It's almost everything everyone else does, except for eating.
I haven't quite figured that one out.
Like I said, you guys, from the report I got from Captain Levi, you've been in the Legionnaire three weeks, already made Omen Knight, specialty class, good for you.
Has it been that long?
It was two years before I got my promotion.
Sorry, your name?
Kaladin.
Dario, nice to meet you as well.
What are your specialties?
What do you guys do?
I got to not turn into a bear.
Nice.
I'm all people.
She goes, huh, I turn into a panther, but not by choice.
Oh, perfect.
Eldritch Knight.
Fighting class, Marshal Levitz.
But understand magic as well.
Ooh, dip your toes.
Jario, I think this one might be kind of a cat in bed, if you know what I mean.
Jesus.
Are you a little boy?
You don't know.
Nobody knows.
Turning into a panther, but not my choice.
I don't know what that means.
I think it almost has to be lycanthropy, which I thought was interesting.
Oh, me?
Yes.
Well, you know, I like to toy around with some things here and there.
I'm not much for fighting.
I don't really care for the... Like a mime hawk does.
You could say that.
Hesitation catches me off guard.
Oh, sorry.
Sorry for your loss.
I'm thought of by choice.
Quick moving, use my fists primarily, but I'm pretty good with a staff.
That's kind of my gist.
And she goes, sorry, but we still technically actively patrol as well, so this is my crew.
And you see some people have filtered in behind her.
That dwarven barbarian woman is in her crew apparently.
She goes, this is Brynja.
She
first.
The axe points to her left behind.
She goes, this is Melistra.
We just call her Lisa.
Sneaky type.
Also female.
Dark skin, but a little more like ashen gray than like brownish.
Hint of elven hair.
Gives a little bit of point to her ears.
Black hair.
Dark stud and black armor type.
We're putting a lot of daggers on her belt.
She just goes,
Too many daggers.
And she goes, and where is, and then you see this little gnome runs through Leora's pants, so small, tiny little red hat, huge, what you know now to be the symbol of the tail, sort of the open palm, but not the curled fingers.
She goes, name's Nim, just to one of you.
She goes, and I heal these fuckers.
pulls out a beer that's like the size of her body, just cracks it, starts chugging, she goes, um, sorry, Brynja, you just lost me 40 gold, you fuck.
Lyra goes, shush now, this is not the time, uh, sorry, we still very much patrol the streets, again, this maturity thing's not really our style, uh,
Once there was a little bit of restructuring, and they said there had to be an officer of the Omen Knights, and we sort of took that as a little bit more pay, but we don't turn down cases.
So, case in point, your case.
Sorry, scattered brain.
She goes, how about you make yourself comfortable in your new bunks?
I will be there shortly.
I know you got a brief rundown of what's been going on, but I've got a little bit of history with this kind of thing, so I will fill you in on things you need to know.
And then she sort of spins on her heel and she goes, that's it, and walks away.
But you see she walks to the bar, just like grabs a nail.
The area that you had talked to that Smithy before, part of that sort of counter space is like a working club for the old Midnights, like for some like downtime.
So it's like a little cafeteria and like it's a little place where you can- This is like a whole sort of like- Gotcha.
All encompassing.
Shared living space.
Yeah, it's a soft serve machine.
You walk into your space and you see that it is very barren.
Three beds for the three recruits, but nothing else.
But it's a big space.
You could put tables in here, couches.
There's enough space in theory that you could put fighting dummies in here if you didn't want to use the communal ones.
It's an open room for you guys to live in.
It's much better.
It's not just like stacked bunks.
You get more than just one little footlocker.
It's a nice space.
Rosario, you're going to have to get more protein in your diet.
There's no spiders in here for you to eat.
I'll figure something out.
And then after a little bit, you guys are getting comfortable maybe putting some stuff up.
Lara comes in, she's like leaning against the door frame, she goes, right, so I know you know the basis of this, and we were on the other side of the market this
I have a history with this.
A few years ago, first in the Legionnaire, there was a lycanthrope case in the Storm District.
It tends to kind of be where it is because the perpetual sort of gloominess makes for odd sunlight hours.
It's much more safer for them to roam.
I had been tracking a, didn't know they were a lycanthrope, but a thief in the alleys and
didn't get cure in time because uh it was a weird passage there was no new moon right away so long enough that it took hold and i lost the chance to sort of remove the curse from my body um so to speak i've also read your file i know you all are esopter cursed make you more adept fighters i am not esopter cursed i am just um cursed like
Yes, I end up killing.
I thought maybe if I killed the were-pamther I would turn back, but not how this works.
Not like vampires, you see.
She goes, so here's what you need to know.
If you get bit, first 24 hours, we can remove it, no problem with the potion.
At your cost, the medbay can do it.
If you know you are cursed, but you haven't had your first try,
from a high cleric at the Medbay for a great cost.
They don't have a lot of the clerics who can perform that, and the cost material components are pretty high.
But as soon as you either have your first transformation or you bypass a week, greater action will be required.
There is possible reversals.
If you let it go, it is permanent.
So there's like a force level of blood.
It wouldn't be Bloodhunter.
I wouldn't force you to multi-class.
You'd have to start tracking the moon cycles in-game.
We wouldn't be able to control it.
she goes and I've done a little bit of research in it from what I understand you manifest different animals it's not always the one that bit you is what you turn into I was bit by a were-rat and I turned to a were-panther I couldn't tell you why but right
Not great in battle.
So now, every once in a while, you'll notice I go dark, I go missing for a while.
I seclude myself to my room when I transform.
Who do we report to whenever you transform?
There'd just be a gap in the cases.
Normally, people are working at that point.
Captain Levi still oversees our section of the Legionnaire.
Very good.
So he'd give you something in that case.
But for the Allman Knights, I'm still...
It's one knight every month or two months or so, depending on that.
That's fair, but...
when they took it down was, and she sort of pulls up a map and she points to it and you see that it is a very similar location to where you were in the storm district last time.
So this is the storm district map instead.
We're saying the core is here towards like the center and the storm district is down here.
It was like you were way southern side last time.
She's telling you like somewhere in here there is like the sighting they just had.
So one of these buildings here is Selina's Potion Shop?
Selina Salve.
So it went club, a couple streets down, and her was the very one on the corner, which is why there was a fungal tunnel that nobody noticed.
Right.
The edge of the area.
Very edge.
the last confirmed sighting and takedown of Lycanthrope was.
What is this building?
This is a great, is this to the graveyard?
When I originally made this map was for our in-person D&D session, so this was the Dawn District, and this was to the graveyard, courtyard, but this is now the Storm District, and don't worry about that.
Okay.
And these buildings?
Random buildings.
Random.
What is the moon face?
is to see them if we are waiting or do we have to try hard?
She has a great question.
Oh, any known weaknesses?
Should we pack some silver with us, perhaps?
Silvered weapons hinder the rejuvenation factor of a lycanthrope.
Magic weapons do damage.
If you want to kill one outright, it has to be finished with silvered weapons once downed.
Otherwise it would regenerate some time later.
What type of were-creature was Celeste?
Uh, last one.
It seems to be mostly were-rats that are sort of coming out of the cities, but there's...
I don't understand how large a were-rat was.
Like five, six feet?
Jesus!
But rats can fit anywhere that their head can, so like it still could get into a pretty tight space if it needed to.
So it's got the head that's like a foot wide, so even though it's like six feet tall, it's just gonna...
Do they sell some silvered weapons, or are those available to us at the... What's-his-butts-at-the-stand over there can get you some silvered powder?
He doesn't sell silvered weapons.
Does that mean we could coat the edge of a weapon with it?
You could get a one-time use exactly, yes, to finish it off.
You, as she looks at you guys, she goes, you guys all rock magical gear, though, so I don't imagine you'd have trouble damaging it, but yes.
Get yourself some silver powder, force it to ingest it upon death, or make a final blow with it.
We don't have many mods.
Can we have silver powder for a mission?
Feels like part of the mission.
We should supply us with what we need.
I printed on syringe potions so that it would not have to charge you those fees.
The ones in your suits weren't good enough?
It's the only ones.
We get crazy.
Okay, um, well... We take down Dragon.
How do you think we got here in three weeks?
Oh, oh, oh, Kaladin, let's, um, you know, just keep that, uh, you know.
Did you get a hoard or something like that?
That's pretty stingy, I suppose.
She goes, well, here, and she, like, she's got a package she pulls out.
She had, like, some silver necklaces.
Do something with that.
You're omen knights, for god's sake.
It's like Mardi Gras.
Not these.
Just one lands on my neck, you know?
You can tell she probably normally wears a silver necklace, but since she was just fighting, she didn't have one.
She's like, oh, fuck.
Here you go.
And she's like, this is not my...
I guess I am your boss.
I don't want to be your boss.
Don't make me be your boss.
I'm just here to give advice to and give you payments.
Well, that's a pretty cool boss.
I always like having cool bosses.
Cheers to the fun bosses.
She drinks as she walks.
Well, when you guys want to head out, you want to head out after tonight.
You got stuff to do, don't you?
You're going to all day it or all night it?
All night, all nighter.
Right, so it's mid-morning, now it's noon.
What time is it?
Yeah, how long is this all day?
I guess I'm just going to fire it off as soon as we get some...
I think it's like noon-ish at this point.
Downtime, yeah.
So do you want to work on this thing for the next 10 hours, and then we try to search at night in the storm district to get a better idea of where...
I guess, yeah.
Would I take a point of exhaustion?
If you did that, you could push yourself harder to finish it before they go out and to go into the night with a point of exhaustion, yes.
And then as soon as you sleep, you'd lose it.
Yeah, so what we should probably do is we should probably sleep during the day.
I just need to meditate.
Yeah.
Well, yeah, I need to sleep.
Actually,
from staying up at night.
So I'll just go in there and I'll, like, throw up some sheets around my bed and make it dark.
And I'll just go lay down.
What's the point of exhaustion?
What does that do?
Disadvantage on ability checks.
That's the first point.
Not so bad.
No, yeah.
Abilities and skill checks.
Yeah, I'll do that.
And then I guess I'll make the sword, presumably.
What is the sword?
What's the stats on it?
It'll be a...
You are not proficient in weapons, are you?
I don't think so.
I don't think so either.
So what we would do when I actually build the weapon, because you rolled high enough to complete it today, it'll be a finesse weapon that uses your intelligence modifier as the main stat for the weapon.
To hit.
Okay.
Essentially, unless you want to change the way it presents in my head, lightsaber adjacent.
Sure.
Long range weapon, you asked me, swords, spear, however you want it to do.
The main thing about the power core was sustained amount of power to project the energy to a certain point or fill a certain space without going over or going under.
So the design is really up to you.
You took the blueprints of how to build the casing to make it work.
But other than that, however you want it to look.
Once you build it that way, it'll stay that way, but you can build it every time.
Would it be a magical item?
It would be magic because it is energy, so...
It's like a lightsaber, but it's just like... Makes that noise.
Okay.
And then, what would the damage?
D8, because Finesse would be like the best, the greatest thing on that is a...
It would be a 1d8, and then I guess, well, like, my hand crossbows are, like, plus 6, like, what's the... Um, proficiency bonus plus attack, and I'd say it'd be, like, a plus 1 weapon, so what is your intelligence modifier?
5.
5, so 1, 6, your proficiency bonus is 3 at this point, it'd be a plus 9 to hit, and then a d8 plus 5 damage, and then if you wanted, we could do fire damage, you could roll, like, a d4 fire damage.
Did I give you the spear?
Were you holding the spear?
You did.
You might just take that back and see if Handlock can eventually do something with it.
Yeah, yeah, I haven't used it at all.
Okay, so you are crafting.
You had an early enough roll that I'm not going to force it.
You get a little tired at first, but you find your second wind pretty quickly, and you start working on it.
And then, like, if...
at this point and you finally finish it and as like it is like you're in the pocket workshop it's on these like forked stance in the middle the handle sort of looks like a lightsaber handle but as you finish it leafle sort of takes a step back what does it do yeah so it is going to take the form of a sword um
And the form factor of the power core is fairly small, it's like the size of an apple, I imagine, or is it a little larger than that?
However you want it to be.
Yeah, yeah, so the, okay.
The power core is roughly the size of an apple.
And that has been kind of crafted into a box that I attach onto my hip.
There is a...
cord that powers the hilt of the sword so that way the sword can never be, you know, basically removed from my person.
And as you activate it, a large glowing beam of crackling red lightning shoots forth and kind of like almost like a scimitar hooks backwards.
um the uh the the color is a gradient of red to deep purple um and on its on its far edge the back side of the blade it wisps off into nothingness so the front edge of the blade is a really blood red and then it kind of wisps away into that violet um
So yeah, I emerge from the pocket workshop and I just, you just start hearing this.
And there's this dummy that was set up as like a little target practice, just like crumbles into quarters.
A pretty rude awakening for you.
Yeah, you are in like your black curtains, just like you draped around your back.
flash in burning intense red light of this curved blade.
It's sort of a little unstable as he finds it.
It's like throwing sparks here and there.
And your whole room goes red, just flaring up.
Well, it's about time for us to get up anyway, isn't it?
I figured as much, yeah.
What has Cal been doing this time?
I think I probably would have spent some of that time practicing in the pits.
Just because.
Yeah.
And then would have meditated for my four hours.
Two hours.
What do I need as an elf?
Is it two?
Four.
Four?
Yeah.
Damn.
Nice.
You're four.
I got six hours.
Yeah.
But I mean, I need to rest.
I need all eight.
You need all eight.
Which I think is the first time you guys have gone into anything with any sort of disadvantage so far, which is cool.
I got a badass sword, so let's fucking go.
Yeah, I already have a disadvantage on stealth, so it fits pretty well.
Just walk around with it.
What the fuck?
It doesn't hum like a lightsaber.
It just crackles.
It's like lightning striking coming out of your hand.
Like one of those towers that you can charge up and if you touch it, it starts... Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're just hearing that like... Yeah.
You guys, I imagine at this point we'll head out and let's see if there's something else you want to do.
So you go into the storm district.
You know roughly the south side of town is where you want to head.
Cool thing before that, actually.
As you guys are making your way out, you see it's like late at night.
Leora's like getting ready for bed.
She's like in her pajamas.
She's got slippers on.
She's got like a cup of tea.
She's walking out like heavy-legged.
She goes, oh, shit, sorry.
Um...
You guys are so used to walking.
Down the hall to the right, Omen Knights have access to your teleportation circles for the city.
Oh, damn.
There are checkpoints on certain points of the wall that can take you to the districts.
You still have to transverse the districts as normal, but it won't be far south side to the core.
You just make it to a wall, and the wall will be able to teleport you back.
um good night she's 13 she keeps walking thank you what is it leora leora l works l even better excellent yes let us move to the circles short walk let's go you guys walk to a room and you almost get a moment of ptsd
established teleportation circle on the ground and he looks and he goes gentlemen and he goes starts plugging he's like where to storm district um right away um teddy will be on the other side of the circle to give you guys an introduction um this is a little bit you guys ever used one of these circles before it'll be a little bit of a maybe a little bit of a head
almost like you're going two places at once it's pretty crazy you'll find out in a moment step into the circles arms and hands arms and feet in the circle at all time do not jump out midway or you might get bisected safe travel you see channel some power into the circle the circles are safe because they're established in two different directions but you notice like in a flash light stretches you feel like your bodies go infinitely high while your feet hit the ground and as soon as
blood out of your head everything your feet come off the ground and they hit the ground again and you are on the top of the wall in the storm district again the storm district is very classically rainy gloomy always sort of overcast but it's dark at this point and it's not raining you know it at this time but through the peak of the clouds you can see an almost full moon in the sky pretty bright coming through so there's like moonlight
But from this viewpoint, you're looking out over the dark city, there's the arcane lights that sort of scatter to give like ambient light on the streets.
The storm district has its own little flavor on them where the lights are like a little bit crackly lightning in there.
So you can see like a little bit of thrumming blue light that sort of lights the city up.
People go in tune from taverns, things like that.
Oh, oh, oh dear.
I think I was going to be sick.
teddy it's okay he's like a giant rotisserie chicken hole just plops out of my uh my headpiece so it just kind of flips back chicken falls onto the ground it's still warm oh there's teleportation circles i think i'd prefer walking to be honest we all remember our first time right
Throwing a chicken up.
Entire whole chicken.
Yeah.
It was alive on the other side.
Well, Zaryl, Kaladin, chicken.
He puts up his umbrella and he's like, I'll be here when you guys are done.
Are we up somewhere at a vantage point?
He said we're on the wall.
You're on the top of the wall looking so like it's poor and then all the districts have the wall so you are on the left wall of it looking into the city so you need to go to like straight other side.
Okay.
Or you can tell Teddy and maybe he can get you to the other side of the wall.
Teleports again.
He's a mage, right?
I don't know about that.
I'm stammering as the circle just starts, yeah.
Dear, I don't know.
We have a pretty good idea of where we're supposed to be looking, right?
We had a map.
You know pretty good.
Quadrant, maybe.
A couple of buildings.
Do we want to sneak?
Do we want to come up with a play?
Or do we want to just kind of...
We are in Omen Knight armor.
I don't know if there's a lot of sneaking.
I think we just need to be quiet and observant, potentially.
Yeah, there's some info.
Omen Knight armor, is it like very bombastic?
It's very like loud colors?
Or is it...
It's very black unless you customize it to be different.
Yeah, let's go down to the buildings where they were last spotted and maybe surveil the businesses.
As we get closer and closer, can I just...
I'll do an investigation check.
Ooh, that's pretty good.
I got a 25.
25, 25, 26.
You must tell us what we see.
Show me the were-rat.
Where is its home?
I was going to look for potential holes or, you know, like you said, the rat can fit through a spot that's as big as its head.
So I was kind of looking for maybe a burrow.
You guys make your way to this strip that you had been on before.
If you remember, there was a club at the northern side of the road that had a line coming out of it.
You would talk to the bouncer who had given you some heads up, and that's when you would see those fungal creatures.
Mm-hmm.
trying to drive that guy into Selena's shop.
You're like walking down that strip.
The club isn't seem to be nearly as loud and bombastic.
There's like some, a lot of noise on the inside, lights, people moving in, but there's nobody out of the door.
So there's no bouncer on the outside, but you're like listening.
And first thing you hear is like some skittering and some shuffling and like hard to describe other than like a dull thud being
hold around on the pavement like you can hear this skidding but it's like not dragging it's like shuffled back and forth weird to describe it like you hear something being moved around something like noise
from where you are you don't super know but then you see um like you're just looking around and then up down the street um up towards say where it would be sailing the shop you see somebody walking and in a moment they're like with like their loved one and they just get like pummeled into an alleyway in an instant you see like something from the other side of the street push them to
out of view we all check that all of you see that as you're like you hear something immediately to your left and then you make eye contact with these people just going for a walk who were just in this moment assaulted okay as an action i'm gonna go ahead and pull my mask out
Just everything gets a little bit brighter.
And I'll go ahead and sprout our little flowers for communication.
Did that get updated again?
Didn't it lose like a little chunk of its energy?
I don't know why it's gone, but I didn't put it in there.
That's okay.
That's the only thing that I think is not there.
We're going to knock it off.
I'm going to retract my steel defender out.
Pull it out of the back plate.
Yeah, he kind of emerges from my back armor.
I'm going to cast Summon the Beast.
Summon the Beast.
Yeah.
And let's see.
a rat terrier eat rats?
Yeah.
I want a giant orange tabby.
Yes.
A giant Garfield tabby.
He's eating lasagna.
Oh, man.
I'm not going to go after those things.
Mondays.
Yeah, Mondays.
All right.
This Garfield just wells forth from the abyss.
Let's see.
Can I talk to it?
They might understand you.
It obeys my verbal command to do the action required by me.
So I'll just be like, all right, Garf.
Be vigilant.
We're looking for some rats.
And then I'm going to wait to wild shape until we get a little closer.
But we're all just going to... Are we going to go for the noise that we heard?
Or are we going to go for... Straight to the alley.
Well, I guess so.
How are we going to get the people though?
Because if the noise is like really close and they're super far.
They were in eyesight.
So three blocks or so by the straight line.
Around the corner of the club was the other sound.
So, 100 feet versus 300 feet kind of deal.
Yeah.
Action and pedestrians versus sound.
That's true.
We should try to save those people.
That's all it is, really.
Yeah, so, yeah, let's just, uh, an action dash, get there as fast as we can.
Sprinting, what are you guys' movements?
Uh, 60.
30 with dash 60.
Yeah, 60.
So, it'll take you a couple rounds to get there.
Garfield's fat ass is way behind us.
Uh, same as me.
Okay.
You guys are sprinting full speed.
Again, a couple rounds together.
You skid slide in sort of the, the rain's like streets of the cobbled stone.
behind in the alley.
You're running down the street parallel with the buildings.
You turn the corner.
This thing goes, whatever it is, up the building and then starts running back the way that you would come from.
The alley.
Can we send Garfield up the rooftop?
Yeah, I'll send him.
I'll tell him to... Don't get him, kitty.
Alright, follow that there thing.
And he's gonna try to climb.
It's technically a spirit.
It says... Let's see...
It has a 30-foot climb, land only, 60-foot fly, air only, and 30-foot swim, water only.
So it can fly.
Yeah.
It says it's got a 60-foot fly speed, but it doesn't really make any sense that it would be double the speed.
But I don't know.
That's what it says.
Flying is easier.
Okay.
All right.
It... Oh, well...
basically just flies, but it doesn't have the difficult terrain.
It crests over the top and you see, can you see from its view?
It just knows.
It sees like a dog-like form.
What we can see is like a werewolf versus kind of a were-other creature bounding over the roof onto the next roof, heading back towards the way you guys had come from.
All right.
Yeah, I'll relay that.
Let's say hello.
Going back where we came.
Let's say back.
Let's go.
And so if it's got a 60-foot fly speed, could it catch this thing, or is that thing faster?
It's going to have a pretty similar movement speed.
It's going to action dash it.
Also, he's not, like, running.
If he's flying, he's just got his paws in like this.
Just like a little potato.
A little loaf.
It was so cool.
It was.
It's got a little piece of lasagna.
It was cool, but now it's not.
So it's running down the alley.
Jonathan, is it anywhere on this map?
So if you guys are here and you turn this corner, it jumped onto this roof and is now on this building heading back this way.
Okay.
So you guys would come back in the street and chase it.
uh i could just have it use its action to try to keep up keep so it's it's like a 30 feet of buildings width kind of yeah and it's just following it yeah and we'll say it gives off a little bit of light if you like so you're like on the ground chasing it from the street and you see the light of it kind of guiding you back thanksgiving day parade yes and it's like loafing through the air um
You guys are chasing it, and eventually it goes back to the alley that you had heard the noise from before.
And as you guys are, like, getting up to the corner, maybe you slow your run, got it ready, you hear some, like, trash cans topple and then just, like, silence.
And the light comes down off the roof and then disappears into the ground because you didn't give it any other commands.
Oh, shit.
It disappears.
I'm going to jump into that hole.
Is that perception?
What would that be?
Perception, yeah.
Okay, all right.
So that's going to be plus seven.
Thirteen.
You don't see one immediately.
Can I yell something?
Well, you don't have to yell.
We've got the flower.
No, it's for Garfield.
Oh, Garfield.
Garfield, meow.
All right.
Can we also make perception checks as we around the corner catch up?
To get any idea or is it just like blank alley?
No.
It's dark at this time.
A lot of garbage, debris, trash cans.
So it's not like your roll was low enough that you didn't see something.
and by the time you lose trail, if that makes sense.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Any better?
I rolled a 14.
I'm going to do an investigation, or does that have to be a perception?
The investigation would take time, so it would be the same deal.
You would have to take time to look, yeah.
Four.
I'm not getting any.
Dead end at this point.
You guys are at the club, though.
Can I go ahead and do an investigation check now?
Try to more thoroughly look for...
where we found this, the entry, where the thing disappeared.
Let's see here.
What is that?
Whoops.
Investigation.
17.
Yeah, something in here.
Eventually, you do find at the base of the building, some of the brick and mortar has been pushed out and the ground has been dug away.
It was sort of like there was a pile of trash bags and it had gone like
passed it underneath, so you didn't see it right away.
Too small for a person to pass through.
I think I found it, but perhaps there's another entrance inside.
It's the club building.
The foundation of the club building.
Well, I've had some experience in that establishment, and I can't say it was a great time.
You were in there before.
Some weird business happening in there.
So the whole...
that we found is too small for a person.
It's like 18 inches and we're all 24 at the shoulders.
Right up to this basement.
Okay.
So yeah, we got the idea.
Well, this thing wasn't a...
Why can't there be?
Yeah, but would it be able to fit in this hole?
It was a dog, small dog.
Small dog.
It was small dog?
Oh, I thought it was huge.
It was dog-like form, but it wasn't a big creature.
So we're thinking get down to the building and I'm going to run up the hole and I'm going to yell as loud as I can.
It's probably way too late by now.
Gar, come back.
Gar, come back to me.
It's bonded to you?
right yeah it does whatever i say recall yeah it's coming back it's like just eventually there's like discord now that whole like toothpaste a couple minutes go behind you see the lights filter out gradually a little loaf your feet your feet feel celestial cat spiritual cat if you don't let like my hand a little bit
It was like a rave event.
It was body to body packed.
Couldn't make anything.
As you guys go into the building this time, it is much less busy.
There are people here chatting.
It is not like a slow night by any means.
What's the day of the night?
We'll say it's a Wednesday.
Okay, and it's what, 8, 9 p.m.?
8 at this point.
8, okay.
So you guys...
You come in through the entrance here.
There are tables set up.
This is normally a huge floor with like a dance stage up here.
When you would come in before, you would like make it a big room and there would be a huge thing going on here.
But there is a nice bar.
There's a back room like porch patio thing.
You see a couple tables, people playing card games, drinking games.
There's like an established game right here.
Fire pit people are chatting.
It is not empty.
It's still kind of busy, but it's not shoulder-to-shoulder.
This is inside?
Yes, fire pit inside.
Is this, what is this little?
Barrels and one of them toppled over.
Okay.
Nice.
There's a toppled over beer can right here.
Let me go speak to the bartender.
Yeah, we need to get it.
get a drink while you're at it.
You walk in, as you sort of like dust off some of the light, it had lightly started raining at some point, passed pretty quickly, so you're not like soaking wet, but shake your shoulders, some of the water come up, people start like making eye contact with you, the police are essentially your kind of deal, but you notice that right...
lingering gazes because of my elf form.
Nothing obvious.
Nobody's really paying that close of attention.
You've got your mask on, don't you?
Yeah, you're like...
He does have a mask on.
A little more into it.
You can be a... Give me a perception check to see if anybody's just staring and I'm going to roll to see if somebody is staring.
You would be looking but as soon as you walk in you hear a voice Right here as his left and the very familiar handsome short thick but full nicely groomed beard and
that you had met before is like, got a lot of jewelry.
He's like, hey guys, welcome back.
It's been some time.
A few weeks, you're right, a few weeks.
You guys look a little bit healthier, a little bit stronger.
Love that.
Look, Brock, we need to speak to whoever owns the establishment.
Oh, you guys are on duty.
Not for pleasure, okay?
Yeah, go see...
He's like sitting on his chair like legs.
He goes, um, Solomon's working the bar tonight.
He can help you out.
Very good, Brooke.
Have a good night, fellas.
I'm going to filter off as people are walking.
What kind of card games do we have going on?
I'm going to try and make some money.
At this table, so you guys like walk in, you're talking with them, you look across, you see a very large, muscular and sort of very heavy, just like full-figured
man, huge beard, wild hair, seems to be running like an arm wrestling table for money, and he seems to be running the floor with everybody.
He is winning back to back, sort of like some gold to get in, see if you can beat him, you can take some money back.
There is a drinking game at these tables, you see people are just kind of going at it,
when he's in good spirit about it and then over here seems to be like an actual organized dice game where people are just rolling to see who can beat you don't really understand the rules yet but it's definitely got money involved in it gambling a lot of fun so there's not a lot of strategy from first glance with the dice it's just kind of rolling seems like a game of luck buying and then you do hear a lot of commotion out sort of in the back but you can't see it because the door is closed got it
Okay, well, I guess with that passing observation, I'll just kind of stick with the squad.
Yeah, well, he's going over to talk to us.
I'll just radio in that, like, maybe we should send somebody to go pick up those dead bodies.
There we go.
Let them know we are on lead already.
Yeah, yeah, we are responding.
Some new dead bodies.
you hear that um you recognize the voice as being i think i said it was nim nim um the gnome that sort of was part of leora's um group goes oh yeah that's that's kind of unfortunate you guys lost one on the first night weird awkward time she goes just fucking with you i'll send out some people in a moment keep us updated obviously
That one's testy.
It's a very vulgar and fucks around a lot.
Hello, Solomon.
You walk to the bar.
You see a taller man.
Again, everybody here has got more of like a Scandinavian theme.
It would be like large beers, lots of jewelry, like unnecessary furs at this point.
Sorry.
he pours some more beer some other people and he goes hey we have few questions we need right now is there a basement and have you seen any unusual animals lately yes a basement it's around the corner of
have to talk with the owner about just letting in some legionnaires understandably but um he's not really keen on on you guys gonna be honest but um understand this they're wanted in murderers perhaps this changes your mind there's always murderers he's sort of like i guess i could be swayed i just give him a high five yeah
nice i'll have uh garfield just started doing that scratching post thing i'm absolutely zero on the edge of the bar zero hey take the water off goes right through it and he goes um sorry rules are rules guys i wish i could buy uh if you get some coin you can buy your way to the back and sneak in but i can't just let you into the cell are you uh you're not allowed in there who's
They are now in your basement.
This is why we need you there.
Perhaps you'd like to interact with the were-dog.
Give me an insight check.
Can I participate in this?
No.
No?
You're not in the conversation.
I'm not there?
You are, but he is leading and he is talking.
Okay, that's fair.
Guidance.
Guidance?
Yeah.
17 plus... 3.
30, 20.
He's not being entirely truthful about knowing versus not knowing that there was a hole on the side of the building.
But he's not giving you any more ground on that.
I telepathically say, I don't believe him.
He knows of the hole.
As just an above-table thing, do we have to, like,
This is Middle Earth.
We do whatever the hell we need.
We are the authority.
We are the law, right?
There are bouncers guarding this.
This is a little more exclusive back area.
But he's like, if you get back there and you get into the basement, I'm not going to stop you.
But he's like, I'm not supposed to let people in there.
I'm going to say I don't think we should just let this push through.
I think we should just go and just say, hey, we don't want
What is this guy's name?
What did you say?
Solomon.
Before we share that, I'll appeal to Solomon.
I'll say, oh, Solomon, well, you know, it couldn't be good for business if your patrons found out you have an infestation of...
infected creatures here.
Well, I'm just saying we're here.
We're going to provide our services of extermination for free.
So, up to you.
You win some coin.
You buy your way into the exclusive lounge.
Don't fucking play the game they have in there.
Whatever.
You can bypass that.
Most people are pretty
phantasmal fighting pit but um they won't be watching you you could probably just sneak into the cellar but um
Well, there's a fighting pay here, too?
It's in the other room.
There's other activities.
Oh, okay.
Yes, of course.
Well, I could spend my way up on the stage belting some lines out if any of these patrons here would.
Nor would I, but there's a show going on in a couple minutes, actually.
Oh, well, mere loss.
Okay.
To the point, you see there is a very, like, a band.
people like lots of furs they're very much embracing the theme of the bar you haven't been here really before you don't know if there's like a regular or not but there's a humanoid looking woman um she's getting ready to put on her set she's got like you know equivalent of like a tambourine kind of yeah she sets up um somebody's actively setting up a little little folk here or do we can we get a read on the genre okay got it stick around long enough to hear it let's
Let's go talk to the bouncers.
Do we need to bribe them or can we just push past them?
I think, yeah.
Yes.
Yeah, I think we... Let's go.
We can just murder these people and I think we'll be fine.
Turn the corner.
Two very large men.
Both about 6'5".
Very muscular.
Very hardened faces.
Look at you.
See that they don't recognize you and go...
In your feet.
Yes, I just unsheathed my sword.
Huh.
Punch Jesus sword.
Entropy.
Puts it down.
You know, the bouncer?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
I reveal my sword.
It goes... Community determination check.
I'll have the cat just flex its claws.
Ah, 16 plus... 17.
Hey!
The whole bar is just red.
The other guy goes to pull his sword before seeing what you're saying.
As you were, gentlemen.
Sheath my lightning sword.
The cattle just receive its claws.
Keeps the low food.
But you guys make your way to this back room.
This back room is dark, poorly lit, but you see flashes of neon blue
over a crowd of 100 people crowding very closely around this thing and as you're walking by you see cellar doors on the left wall to the ground on the right you see some guy leading some sort of betting ring and there are um you see like glass orbs in everybody's hands they're kind of like in a line and you see that they very much are like two people stand on the side
an animal of some kind.
The other person throws out, and it projects an animal, and then their animals fight as they place bets on it.
I choose you.
But as you guys make your way to the cellar to work... Where do you get an orb?
Well, you guys didn't want to do that, so you're going right to the cellar.
You go to the cellar, and you don't want to play the games.
That's fine.
It's not locked.
It's inside the building, so they don't feel like they need to...
As you were making your way down the stairs, you hear like the woman give an introduction of her group and everything.
And then she starts singing so that the whole music of the whole area changes as she starts doing like the performance in the background as you guys make your way underneath the building.
You are in the cellar.
It's pretty dark.
There's no traditional arcane lamp down here, but you see there's some torches that you can light on the wall if you'd like with your immediate darkness.
shelves, some barrels that are tapped.
You see the ones on the wall have a line going up to the top, probably to the bar itself.
You can see?
Do we see any, like, claw marks or signs that something feral has, like, gone through here?
You got drool, blood, blood, claws.
You check, like, the walls of the room, and you see that there's not a break in the wall to this room, so whatever the tunnel was bypasses.
As you're searching, give me another round of investigations as to what this would be more like.
These creatures would be magical?
no which creatures the the where the where creatures uh 16 they would no 17. um i thought it was mines but it's positive are you well i have this as ritual i can cast detect magic what is that 10 minutes not not magic like that no okay got it uh 22. um oh plus 10 takes you a while but you find that
upturned dirt on, like, you walk in technically on the west side, and I said it was on the other, it's on the east side, so you go around behind the stairs that you came in on, you see there's like some freshly upturned dirt underneath.
Freshly relative, but it's not flat, padded down, packed dirt as the rest of it.
Can I dig in there?
Can I see how big this hole is?
You were digging in, and you see that it's filled, as far as you can tell,
but it's not packed.
So you're digging and you're not, it's like you're digging into a hole, but it's really easy to dig in.
You figure if you had a way to mass remove dirt, you might breach into a tunnel at some point.
If it's spiritual, is it material?
It can fight.
What's the duration on this?
It's an hour.
That seems a little broken so far, but an hour's fine.
We'll say 20 minutes in.
So, in your head, you're about a third of the way through, but yes, Garfield just starts digging.
commit us to 20 minutes no 20 minutes has already gone by oh oh you guys have been chatting so you're about a third way through the spell but it you can just commit it to do that and as it's digging through eventually you find that like it breaks through the top of like the dirt and you can move enough dirt that yeah there is like a person-sized hole that goes into the ground
Going down?
Yes, we go down.
It looks like we're going down.
All right, I'll have Garthil go first.
Give me a little light, because I don't have dark vision.
And then I'll just start crawling the direction.
I'll tell him to go the direction that he came from, because I assume he bent through here, right?
Mm-hmm.
I would assume he'd been through here.
I don't know if you've got a direct communication line with it, but this is not the same tunnel.
Oh, okay.
So he wouldn't know.
So I'll try to tell him to go the way he came, but if he's like, eh, then I'll just tell him to go that way.
You tell him to go the same way, and he goes down and gives you a weird look and shrugs his cat's shoulders like, I've never seen this before.
And it doesn't take you long to figure out that this was like...
Seems like this was a tunnel that was being used that is no longer the main way, so they closed it off.
So this will lead you into the tunnel network right underneath this.
You don't know where it leads necessarily, likely the right place, but this is not his tunnel.
Well, we should keep trucking, so we should be crawling.
We're going to have to drop into the space.
Yeah, the spirit's really helpful.
I got it to help in combat.
So you guys drop in here.
Nice, okay.
Now can we stand or are we crawling?
It is hard for you to stand all the way if you are hunched forwards at all times.
If you are normal height, under 6'6", you'd be close, but you could make your way pretty easy.
Yeah, I'm fairly tall.
You said you were like 6'7", 6'9", something crazy like that.
Yeah, I'm fairly large.
6'11".
6'11", yeah, you cannot stand up.
455 pounds.
Yeah, boy!
I'm a big boy.
My skin is made out of hardened steel.
So do we want to sneak, or do we want to just... We can try to sneak.
So...
He can stay there until we're ready to have a barrel on him.
Any inanimate object.
Does it have to stay 20 feet back?
Pretty much.
Is this okay?
I was going to say, I feel like my own stealth is all right.
I got a little good.
Well, if we really wanted to, I could burn the pastoral, well, let's see, it's concentration.
Burn what?
Pastoral, but he's got his beast up.
I mean, I could drop the beast, but... We can keep using the beast.
He'll be a third, he'll be a fourth fighter.
Yeah, well, the thing that, it seems really awesome, but AC is 11 plus the spell level, so it's 13 AC.
what's its damage normal because i just have way too high basically what's its damage do uh like a 1d8 plus okay 1d8 plus 4 plus the spells level in piercing damage and then it's my spell attack to attack so it's better that's basically my steel defender i mean it can do a little bit more well i gotta burn the second spell every time yeah okay
Can we begin to slowly pad forward?
Can we ask Leopold to not move?
Can we ask him to stay back?
Oh, shit.
I guess it doesn't matter.
I was going to say his skills are at disadvantage, but your stealth is already at disadvantage.
For what?
Well, you're exhausted.
Oh, yeah.
Can you get double disadvantage?
No, I
I got a 17.
I got an 11.
Do I roll for the spirit?
I'll go off of this deck.
Plus zero.
Ooh, that's cool.
That's 17 on the roll.
Nice.
Very well.
It's silent.
Overall, high and quiet.
We'll just see if you get noticed.
Nothing immediately.
You're making your way down this tunnel system.
Your vision only goes so far, but eventually, you get on this corner and you hear movement down sort of this way, as you're sort of at this corner.
Flea fold is still at the entrance.
Hey, I'm up, guys!
Just hear this echoing.
So can we peek around the corner and see if we see anything?
I don't think I have dark vision.
Bren, you have dark vision, right?
I have dark vision.
Nice.
Man, I've got it too, so.
Although, I'm not anywhere close to you guys.
There.
Well, it's funny that in my language it says telepathy, but not...
I think maybe I just put it there.
The mask, yeah, maybe just plugged it over there.
Again, I don't know where it went.
So just Kaladin is moving up there.
Well, I'll stay with him.
I mean, as far as I know myself, I'm just not going to get all the way up around the corner.
So it's Kaladin.
Who are these?
The cat.
Ah, the cat.
Yeah, the cat will just be floating right behind me now.
Back here a little bit.
I want to be close enough that I can help.
You see movement down here.
You've got dark vision to 60.
I think even further now with the mask on.
Jesus.
Dark vision is greyscape vision.
It's not color.
So you see dark shapes and you see two forms sort of moving back on here.
And one of them, really low to the ground, moving, like, mid-walk, and it's, like, all four, stands up and shifts into a humanoid, shakes off, sort of, like, digs something.
You see, like, its leg comes up, like, really dexterous, sort of, like, at its ear.
Inhuman point.
And the other one goes...
You can do advantage because of your ears.
Can I also?
Your long ears give you a little bit of a bonus.
That's a 16 plus 5, 21.
Nice.
You do hear, it's like broken at this point, but one of the voices is familiar, one of them is not.
One of the voices you just hear is, good hunt.
Love that.
And the other one goes, yeah.
voice you do recognize.
The second one.
I think maybe I've come across that guy before.
You would be the one to really remember.
Yes.
You give me a history check to see, but since you guys left Leopold's
I don't think I was there for that interaction.
You were outside, so you met the person briefly.
Kaladin came and rescued me from the...
So what would it be to recognize?
I rolled a 73.
Okay.
Do you recognize that voice?
I rolled an 18.
Sounds like the voice of Terrence.
That little, like, scruffy dwarf kid who had the fake vampire teeth in him.
In lines?
That's what I thought the voice was.
He was, like, for reintroducing him.
He's, like, fake.
grinding up on Leopold.
Trying to get me to do some drugs.
Is this model after someone you went to high school with?
No?
Isn't that a kid named Terence's?
There was.
He was weird, but no.
I love that.
Yes, yes, but no.
This was originally a card that I remember.
Okay, okay.
Maybe it's a little bliminal.
Maybe.
I would relay this to be our telepathic bond.
So he probably got bit on purpose, you little freak.
You guys, Terrence, your friend, Leopold, was here.
Oh, dear.
I wouldn't call him my friend.
Perhaps it's the curse.
There's another two, so I only see two people.
We can attempt to move forward, confront these two.
I don't know if there are more.
Yeah, we'll have to see them.
At this point, trying to be stealthy, you need to be giving me a new check.
Otherwise, you can get up to the corner.
Up to that point.
Are we calling that like another 25, 20 feet?
What are you calling that?
Yeah.
What's another turn to get close enough?
What's our final distance going to be if we get to right here?
50, 60 feet across?
This is 30 feet to the corner is how I had it.
Okay.
So like 30 feet, 60 feet, and that would be like 100 feet.
Are both of them going to be within 30 feet or is one of them going to be further?
They're somewhere in here.
You are not there yet.
You are walking up, so you don't have eye contact with them.
You don't know where they are in the room, but you hear them talking.
So, would it be safe for me to approach now that they've kind of cleared this cavern, or would that still be... As soon as you start moving, you need to give me a stopwatch.
Wait, we'll tell you when to move, Leopold.
30 feet, 20 feet, and then another 30 feet.
You are 80 feet.
You take a full action just to get into the battle.
You take a while to catch up.
You take one round to get into the battle range.
Okay.
And above you, you're still close enough.
You do hear the music playing.
So, like, the band is singing.
Oh, so that's covering sound-wise.
Yes, there's a lot of noise, like...
You got there earlier tonight.
You think, like, the main act is starting, and you hear, like, a lot of people moving.
There's, like, it's mostly cavern space, but occasionally you'll see, like, a wooden floorboard that, like, people shuffle over and dust filters in.
Yeah.
All right.
I think with that, I'm just going to try and get here.
Close at least 30 feet.
Give me a stealth check with disadvantage.
Eight.
Eight?
Yeah.
They hate with disadvantage.
It's a pizza, they hear you.
So, you are got like this point of visibility.
Fuck.
It's so loud.
We're in a concert.
Your suit of armor just catches it.
There's like the muffled singing above you.
So far away.
Filters down the hallway.
And you hear, Hey guys, how's it going?
Out of nowhere, they're having a conversation and he goes, Wait, I think someone's here.
Coming around the corner, you see Terrence so sweaty, his hair's like matted, his spotty beard is matted to his face and he's got some blood around his mouth.
He looks more muscular.
He's got no clothes other than, like, a leotard on at this point.
He was just a chubby, undefined, unathletic person before.
He's got, like, pecs in, like, a pot ab belly where it's, like, muscular, but he's still not trying very hard.
And he goes, as you come to meet your demise, show your self.
How far away is he?
He still has plastic surgery.
He's still wearing it.
The one that was 60 feet off amongst a rock concert that you could hear.
Clang, clang, clang, clang.
It must have tripped and tumbled into a pile.
Don't move for a while, everything just stiffens up.
You gotta move, it just breaks everything free.
Oh, Jesus.
Jonathan, what happened?
What about access to that spell we talked about?
Mm-hmm.
that you would know but like if you try to do it you would like manifest if you wanted to okay then maybe not yet i'm just gonna can i close the distance on this is this like are we rolling initiative now that they've seen us so far he hasn't just attacked you he's talking he's like speaking into the dark he probably has dark vision he can see forms but he doesn't know what's going on so he's like sort of by time maybe he's talking to you guys
Even if we didn't think this guy was killing people, we should probably kill him anyway.
We should probably fuck him up.
He's got a curse.
Also, I have the steel defender there.
We need to kill this guy.
Yeah, I think I would just get the jump on him.
Can I go ahead and just cast Chromatic Orb at first level?
Yeah.
Just reaction blast him.
Terrence is getting fucked.
His whole torso is just getting ripped out.
That's going to be 16 to hit.
16 hits?
I don't have a good feeling about this.
Where should I kill this poor lackey?
Three, ten, thirteen.
Good sign.
We'll say, can it be one of six damages?
We'll just say fire damage.
You throw, and the fire, as it shoots through the air, lights the perimeter of the tunnel as it travels through, a little bit behind the plastic.
And he's in the middle of this weird monologue that he did not burn the right thing.
as smoke and ember comes off his shoulder, and you hear the other form goes, oh, what the fuck?
And you don't see anything, but you hear, like, skin-tearing sounds, just like, as this other form comes into place, and you hear a heavy thud with, like, snorting sounds.
He's a were-pig?
Were-bore, thank you.
Were-bore.
I have a disadvantage on initiative as well.
Yes.
On everything.
Six.
Let's see.
Oh, ten.
Yeah, plus two.
Twelve.
It's too bad.
What do I have?
Twenty-one.
Well, I guess I wouldn't have rolled two dice.
Okay.
Okay, 25 to 20.
I was hoping they'd go and have the cat attack or something, but it's okay.
The cat was caught off guard.
He's, like, cleaning himself.
Choking on a hairball.
Smoke him while he's down.
You don't come to meet your demise?
I don't think that's unusual, right?
Yeah, where they're just sitting around in a completely dark cavern.
Yeah.
Talking to each other, completely blind.
When you walked in, they had been in different forms, and they just transformed.
Okay.
Back to their kingdom.
They didn't light any torches yet.
Nothing yet.
Got it.
He's on his way to the light of inspiration.
Yeah.
They just sit around in pitch black.
They're near something else.
Yeah.
This is not exact.
You don't know where this guy is.
You heard something behind the corner, which you can't see.
That's fine.
I'm going to do just that.
I'm going to poke my head the rest of the way around the corner.
So a little bit of movement.
Turning the corner, you've got dark vision.
You see full charge, not having taken a turn yet, but in the action of
grown monsters this is like that but just um exacerbated lit but all of its features are
I guess they extend strength.
Now I'm also concentrating on that, so I'll have to remember that.
Terrence on the ground.
Strength saved.
It's just the restrained condition is what it looks like.
Fails.
Other figure.
To save.
18 plus 3.
21.
Passed.
Does that stack?
There's two difficult trains on top of each other?
It's just flat, difficult.
So he'll move into it on his turn tentacles, like right on the outside, but you see like the vines reach up on it.
It's all, it's full, it's in a full
fully gets entangled on the ground, does not save on that.
Next up is... Is that the end of your turn?
Yeah, it's the end of that one.
Okay, the boar.
You see it will keep in its fourth form.
Does anything happen if a creature ends its turn?
I think it's every time it's in...
Each creature other than myself must succeed on a strength saving throw within the area or have a restraining condition until the spell ends.
A restraining creature can take an action to roll a strength or an athletic check against the spell DC on its success and frees itself from the plants and is no longer restrained by them but still...
What is the restraint condition?
Essentially zero movement speed.
But you can still attack?
It attacks on creatures other than what's restraining it or disadvantage.
So it can attack the vines at regular or everybody else at disadvantage.
So you said you're here, it's like 20 feet, but it's like 20 feet to you.
So does it make a new save at the start of this turn?
If it's entering.
Technically, you cast it to have it hit, so it's already in it.
No, so then I'd say it's already past it.
The plants will no longer try to entangle it, from what I understand.
It has 40 feet past.
and then you also make it.
So give me a DC 13 strength save every knock prone, but it'll also roll the hit for the attack.
Well, that's an 8.
Right.
I would assume if it misses, then you'll just miss this, yeah.
That's a 3 plus 5.
It does an 8 hit.
Negative.
So the charge doesn't do anything extra because it misses that, but it'll do... You said a strength check?
Yeah, you don't have to make it because it missed the touch.
It makes two attacks, only one of
You didn't put the shield up right away, just missed.
Do it later.
Okay, and that is its turn.
Next up is Terrence.
You see on the ground, just, oh, fuck.
Prepare to take me at my worst.
And you see, just gets a little bit taller and turns into a,
action to do it.
hit point cool on it or something like that?
Let me pull that spell back up.
He can only make two attacks.
He'll bite, and he's got technically a short sword, so he'll do both.
I don't think they can free themselves by hacking.
He doesn't know that he's going to just slash at it.
The vines are going up on him at the same time.
He's fully laying prone still at this point.
He cannot get up after that as Leopold.
Um, so I was going to say, what did we say?
30, 30 feet to like, to the corner.
Like you get back to Garfield's you're 30.
Oh, okay.
So, um, and still,
My still defender has slightly further.
He has 40 feet.
So I'll get here and still defender can be there.
Is that 10 feet?
Okay.
Halfway between them.
I don't know what, what's a typical reach five feet.
So he's still 10 feet away.
Um, but
With my attack, I will do... All creatures, I don't want to do that.
I will cast Ray of Frost on Terrence.
Little Terry.
He is prone to disadvantage.
Oh, for being prone.
Yeah.
Because it's like a smaller space.
Ah, I didn't know that.
Then I'll go after the board.
What's really funny is when somebody's like ten feet away and you're like shooting at them.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's like laying on the ground.
How?
Uh, so with my, uh, action, I will do Ray of Frost on the boar.
To do that, you would have to hit Leopold, uh, sorry, uh, Kaladin as well.
Isn't Ray of Frost single target?
Uh, that's what I was thinking.
Uh, frigid beam of blue-white light, ranged spell attack, uh, on the target.
Perfect.
Oh, and its speed is reduced by 10 feet.
So then with the vines, you'll have an additional 10 feet reduction.
Okay.
Yeah.
And...
Got it, so that's a... Yeah, plus eight to hit, so 18.
And that'll be 2d8.
I've got one here.
Wait, these are d10s.
Those are games.
You can roll that if you want.
Yeah, I was just going to let it roll.
He's like, weird, how am I doing so well?
Six, seven damage on the Ray of Frost.
And his movement is reduced.
To ten feet or by ten feet?
By ten feet.
Yeah, by ten feet.
Still good, 15 pizzas.
And then with my bonus action, I will cast Magic Stone to bring up some stones.
And that's my action.
Sorry, you're up.
Am I going to have any trouble getting anywhere?
my action to... Well, before I do anything, I'm going to say to Garfield, I'm going to say, you know, help us kill these two fuckers.
And he's just going to go...
He's going to make an attack on...
Can he go here, or does he have to go around?
He'll have to go around.
Actually, he has pack tactics, but to give Kaladin an advantage, I'll have him swing around here, and I'll have him attack.
As my action, I'm gonna transform into a bear.
So I'm just going to have to try to stay close to his little glow so I can see.
So I'll just move to right here, not knowing this is difficult terrain.
That's what?
20?
20 feet?
What's that?
So I can get, like, another 5 feet.
I can't get any further.
5 feet half.
So, yeah, you just, like, step onto it.
Yeah.
Give me some Drake Saving Throne to enter it.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, there's that.
Yeah, because this is a...
Strength save.
This is control.
Still slow, but you don't get stuck, but you're like right close to being you're not in range of it yet.
All right, this is Okay, so Garfield will attack
He's going to get advantage for his attack tactics, so that's going to be plus 7 to hit.
Breaking 11.
19.
Then he does 1d8 plus 4 plus 2, so that's going to be 2 plus 6, so 8.
I'm almost positive that's what it is.
Did you guys kill Terry yet?
One pounce away.
Oh, that's just an egg with all your beans in it.
That's going to be eight damage.
Oh nice, somebody's Vega?
Is there a Steel Defender?
I'm going to keep it as the d6.
So this guy was only an 11 to hit?
Yeah.
That tells me that this is a big fight.
He's the bad, bad.
These are just the peons.
No, no, this is it.
Where's the final level?
Maybe we should incapacitate him.
Get some information.
You want him to bite you?
You can't turn into a were-thing.
You're not a person.
Up to top of the order?
I don't know if it matters for me.
Calvin.
I'm gonna... Now that this boar is kind of surrounded, I'm gonna misty step over to Terrence.
I'm gonna yell at him.
Who turned you?
Tell me who.
And I'm gonna go ahead and take another swinging attack out of advantage.
Okay.
Got 22 to hit.
Yeah.
call it radiant damage on the additional.
Oh, that's awesome.
So it's, yeah, four and four.
So that's seven, 11 points for four of its radiant.
I never noticed that before.
Yeah.
They're, they're glitter liquid.
I just, I just noticed that really fun.
Yeah.
Good damage, a lot of damage.
You don't know that the Radiant seems to do anything more so than the other stuff.
But good damage on that still.
Any of your turn?
Bonus action action?
Yeah, bonus action, misty step action, swing.
Okay.
Next up will be the boar then.
Having lost you in front of it, it'll turn to...
This hasn't done anything to it yet, has it?
for a little cat.
Fuck him up.
The first one will be a tusk at you and then it'll be a ball on the spiritual.
Well, you don't know that.
I've been rolling pretty garbage.
Tusk.
Natural 20.
On me?
Jesus Christ.
It's doing a little dance right now.
is 16 plus 5 21. okay they both i was rolling like four and three before it wasn't the cat has an ac of like 12. i think it's 11 plus my spell level which is 213. okay uh i need any advice for this stuff 2d6 plus three on
It might be a roll if there's a contact.
So I was like, don't hit it.
You take 8 plus 3, you take 11 points of slashing damage.
Give me a DC, I'm gonna tell you what, constitution saving throw.
Never mind, it's not relevant.
I'll do this first.
So I have a plus 3 in this form, so 15.
And then I have to maintain... Do I use my mental stats, not physical stats?
So I get advantage on this to maintain Garfield.
17.
Wait, so am I within 5 feet?
No.
Yeah, it is.
like the first one.
No, this is you.
This is like 15, 20 feet.
From the skill defender to the boar, is that 5 feet?
10.
15 if we're playing on our usual grids.
The D4 is almost there.
The D6 is almost a grid.
Okay, and then on the spiritual thing,
So that, you said 8?
Yeah, so I'll just try to remember 12.
Did you say it's got 20 total?
Yeah, yeah, 20 total, so now it only has 12.
I'll just count out to 12.
Okay, sounds good.
Okay.
Um, after that is Terrence.
Uh, it's, you're at him.
Um, action to break out or disadvantage tactic.
So far he's been very successful, so.
He's not strong, he's not going to try to break out.
He is going to... You see, he's going to try to slash your ankle and then bite you at the other ankle at the same time.
Disadvantage on both short sword.
15 and 16 on the die, so he gets a plus 4.
That is 19 to hit.
I think that would make a hit, Brent.
He has a shield to make it miss.
Okay, so the short sword misses, which means that he's still disadvantaged.
so don't worry about that second one that's in his turn leopold you are up uh yeah i'm gonna close the uh the gap i'm gonna whip out my laser sword and uh roll to hit you said that was a plus nine yes okay
19?
Oh, okay.
Let's see if we get a... No.
And then it was 1d8 plus... a d4 plus 5?
Okay, so that's 7 and then... yeah, so 12 damage.
on the slice and then with my bonus action I will hurdle a stone I don't know if I can sidestep just without or maneuver a little bit so that way I can right through to Terrence if you roll an at one you'll hit one of them but otherwise you can make it okay so go ahead and roll disadvantage you're at
No, no.
That's the second level.
That's the second?
Okay.
But it does have disadvantage because it's prone.
Yes.
I remember disadvantage for that.
I was like, oh shit, should be a disadvantage.
Okay, so disadvantage on the prone...
3 plus 9 you're just dead plus 8 so 11 just misses AC 12 so the stone flies wide hits the wall behind and sparks off there
That's my heart's terror, Leopold, but I am.
As the Steel Defender goes?
Steel Defender rolls in.
This is a walled corner, so you can't go into there.
Okay, yeah.
Sorry, you can push me sideways.
Yeah, I was going to say, is there some space for the Steel Defender?
No, you guys are on all four sides.
No.
There's no space for the Defender?
Not for this.
The Defender could enter the room, but...
Okay, so the Defender... Could the Defender pass by to attack?
Okay.
As it enters that space...
See, it doesn't pull up for whatever reason, but it does show here.
I just have to find it because it's buried.
Yeah, Steel Defender.
14, okay.
So that's plus two.
21.
Okay, so he'll do a Force-Empowered Rend, which is... 1d8 plus proficiency bonus.
So it has a damage?
It has advantage because the player is prone.
Right, I was just trying to find the modifier to hit.
It should be the same as your spellcasting modifier.
Okay, so plus 9 then.
And it's with advantage.
So that'll hit.
14 plus 9.
Yes, that'll be 8.
Do-do-do-do-do-do.
five and then it's plus my proficiency bonus so three so eight damage on the yep Terrence is looking hurt take that Terrence that's my turn okay back up to
attack as a bird that's gonna be uh plus seven so i'm gonna make two attacks uh bite and claw on this guy with advantage because he's surrounded 22 for the bite and uh dirty 20 for the claw both hit all right the first one's gonna be 1d8 plus five piercing
Slashing for the Claws.
2, 4, so 6 plus 5, 11 on the Claw.
And then...
I'm gonna have Garfield make an attack with advantage.
It's gonna be a plus 7 to hit.
He only gets one attack, but it's advantage.
That's gonna be 18 to hit.
Okay, that's 1d8 plus 4 plus 2.
that's gonna be six um 12 uh piercing damage damn cat puts out some damage that's my uh does your spiritual whatever
Okay, so it's just halved is all.
A little bit better still.
I think my form has magic damage.
Let me double check the old form.
You're a bear.
I know, I thought I had something in my last thing that said that my attacks were magical as my form, but let me double check the first one.
But yeah, that's my whole turn.
Okay.
Uh, at the very top of the order, Kaladin, you're up.
Yeah, it says my beast form counts as magical attacks for overcoming resistance.
I'll give you a level 6.
It's called, uh, Primal Strike.
Perfect.
Alright.
Terrans again.
Who terran'd you?
Where are they?
He was gonna respond last time, so I'll give him a response now, before you kill him.
where that form is like teeth sticking out.
His nose is like up and down.
He goes, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
It was a wild night.
I don't totally remember.
Everybody was giving out these syringes.
It was crazy.
That's all I remember.
And then the full moon happened and I had a great night.
And now I just come back here.
I'm assuming that started my whole conversation.
Don't hurt me.
And it'll take another attack with advantage.
Wait!
Got some silver dust on that blade.
That's a 16.
Hasn't put it on yet.
It'd be a bonus action to apply.
21 to hit.
But you guys never ground it down, did you?
The silver?
No.
Okay.
Well, if you wrapped your sword in a necklace that had silver on it and stabbed somebody, would that do it?
It's not silver.
It's silver.
Without completely eviscerating to the point where he couldn't heal because he's going to, how do you want to finish him for now?
Um, I think Light Splitter would just plunge, like, deep into his chest as he's just, like, super fine.
Just gets sort of uncovered by Vines at that point.
Blade hits and it goes through into the factor.
You just feel a little bit of give as you, like, sever his spine.
Pull it out.
Body doesn't respond.
Completely limp.
Then do your turn.
Do I sense anyone else?
We haven't said anything.
Does this just end?
Is there anything over there?
You look up and you don't see any other forms at this point.
Board turn.
It's going to take an attack on... Give me...
Roll d20s.
Lowest is getting the tusk.
Let's get
get them all let's go not likely okay not high enough to see our healer okay
23 to hit.
They also did get hit by frost damage, so that would prevent healing, right?
Yes.
Well, that's a chill touch.
That's its own deal.
It's not just frost damage.
20 to hit.
20 does not hit.
Goddamn.
You got to hit me with a 21.
I'm over here with a 12.
No, as a bear.
Yeah.
You said how much, sorry?
Eight.
So werewolf thing translate into your bear form?
I wouldn't imagine so, it's a curse.
So plus three.
So six.
Okay.
Don't just okay me.
You know, wait.
Am I within, now within five feet with this?
Nah, you're too far.
Still?
Yeah, you're beyond.
I'm good.
So, 17.
So I drop Garfield.
Wait, did he attack me or did he attack Garfield?
He attacked you and then he attacked Leopold.
But missed Leopold.
Okay.
On this turn, you see that Terrence just sort of like the body kind of like moves underneath the vines and you hear like a
As the spine corrects and the cutovers just closes, he doesn't come back to consciousness right away.
Healed because he wasn't killed with the silver weapon.
Unconscious, but killing him, he likes it.
He does.
Oh, yes, again.
My turn.
I will make another strike against the boar.
with my energy sword.
That would be with advantage, right?
So just flank in.
That would be 18 to hit.
Cool.
And then that would be a 1d8 plus four.
That's 10, give me an eight.
Give me a four.
four damage, but then plus five, so nine damage.
Nine damage with the sword.
And then with a bonus action, I will do a magic stone on the boar.
And that would be with disadvantage because I'm so close, right?
Or I guess it would be a flat roll because I have advantage from flanking.
yeah okay 14 plus 8 hits and that's a it's because I put it I put it in for the skill defender
four and plus five, another nine damage with that stone.
So 18 damage total.
And then with that is Leopold's turn with my Still Defender.
He will retrace some steps.
And that would be with advantage, correct.
19 plus nine would hit.
And that's,
One d8 plus three, yeah.
Blue line.
Four damage.
And that's my turn.
Okay.
Zario's up next.
Yeah, I'm gonna go ahead and attack twice as a bear.
Damn, Zario.
That's gonna be a plus seven to hit.
bite that's uh 10 piercing damage on the bite and then 2d6 plus five on the claw it's gonna be two plus six plus five eleven on the bite and then garfield's gonna take another attack how would you like to finish up for now um let's see um it's a boar so as a bear i'm just gonna take a big chunk out of it and just like bite it grab the back strap just
Pick it up by like that thick of its neck.
Tearing it around, back and forth, back and forth, and eventually you hear its neck snap as you throw it up against the wall.
Drops, unmoving.
How far is it from here?
I don't have difficult terrain because it's floating, right?
Yeah.
Okay, so I'll just have to... Oh, he's already dead.
Unconscious.
Yeah, I don't think the cat can do anything.
It didn't do anything, so...
I should probably drop my bear form.
I'll wait.
I'll just chill.
That'll be my turn.
As the fight sort of drops and you guys are out of combat for this moment, the forms, again, not dead, slowly healing, putting themselves back together.
You can sort of pick up on the music above you again as you just sort of notice the singing again.
feel is that
Do something different.
Do you guys have this dark cavern in front of you?
Does he still have a hole in his chest where I stabbed him?
It's healed now.
Yes.
Can we restrain these guys?
Well, he's already restrained.
With the vines, but... With the boar?
But as soon as he wakes up, he gets to roll.
We gotta kill these guys.
We don't have any way.
Can I stab him again?
chest.
I'm going to pull the silver necklace out that I have.
I'm going to wrap around the aedric arch and I'm just going to start sawing the arch.
Saw his head off?
No, just the aedric arch.
Saw the heart out.
Makeshift weapon would do one point of damage anyway.
You kill him with a silver weapon.
Eventually, Les starts spurting all over your face and your chest and your arms and your hands.
It's like a bloodbath of a scene.
You guys see Kaladin do
And he gets up and he's soaked on his face and his chest, and he's just covered in blood.
We need a silver dagger.
Oh, Jesus Christ, Kaladin!
Remind me never to make you angry.
A silver spoon.
I'll drop my form.
Do I get the impression that a lesser restoration would have anything to do with this?
Oh shit, I don't have time.
I don't even have it up.
Never mind.
I don't have it up.
Uh, so... Let's see if you treated it really quick.
We only have this silver necklace.
We just have a couple of them.
Okay, oh, I'm gonna take a silver piece, coin, and I'm gonna load it into my chest.
And I'm gonna...
and stuff you can make dust and this coin is just gonna fly out of my chest cavern into the right through its chest um body just like lurches and drops and you see when you finish it with it and same with Terrence when you finish sawing through his aorta garden um the body's revert back into the human forms this other person just looks like a regular guy dark black messy hair average height pretty thin build nobody you've ever seen before hmm
Can we take a second?
Are there any other signs of maybe...
any organization are they planning something or is this just their little den and it's just like a little round you see in here uh this just looks like a living space there's like straw heaps put together on the ground like they put together a comfortable place you notice there's a lot more places to lay than there are things in this room but these are the only two in here that you you've taken a moment you're just kind of hanging out nothing kind of comes in at this point
So nothing interesting over in that corner?
Yeah, do we get the impression that that's been traveling recently?
As you sort of turn and go down that way, there is like a tunnel above your head that Garfield starts doing little spins and back flips around, pointing to.
That's where one came in.
Not this tunnel here, but one right above it.
Yeah, like it connects through the top.
And you see, looking around, there are side tunnels all over the place.
Little holes and reliefs in the walls, things like that.
But the other one's large enough for us to travel down?
Yes.
So the relief tunnels could easily backfill with some creatures or something, presumably.
Let's keep moving.
So yeah, do we want to just head down that tunnel?
Mm-hmm.
Do we want to take, does anybody need anything for a short rest?
Does anybody want anything?
I mean, I don't, if you need to, I'm fine to.
I'm good.
I mean, I've used some spells and stuff, but.
I've used a couple of ones with Chromatic Orb and two Shield Reactions.
Okay.
I haven't used any spells yet, so.
I'm okay.
All right.
Well, I still got, like, what?
How long was that?
Five minutes.
Five minutes, yeah.
That was three rounds.
So that wasn't even a full minute, but the travel time and everything.
So yeah, about 30 minutes left on Garfield.
Yeah, let's check out this other tunnel.
Yeah, let's head on down this way.
Do we want to be quiet?
Of course.
I'll hang back here.
Stay back.
All right, so yeah, we'll head down.
Doesn't matter how loud they are.
We'll head down this way.
So stealth, roughly six seconds later.
with the one that I rolled on that before.
You hear a... Just farther down in a direction that you can't see.
In a tunnel, not... Not directly above you.
Not coming in.
Just rather quickly, they were able to sort of track down the sort of location of it.
Stealth, do you want a stealth check?
So we're just here, we make note of that, we hear it.
You hear that?
Up to you guys what you want to do.
Stealth, you want to run?
Up to you.
Nothing else has happened.
Should we just run?
We can run through the tunnel.
Yeah, let's just run.
You guys have already left.
Leopold, let's go.
I was going to be sitting there, like, hanging out.
You guys, I'm going to just makeshift something real quick for fun.
This tunnel is long, hundreds of feet, barely wide enough to go more than one person.
You could, like, run, squeeze by sideways, but as far as single file for most of it, you guys hear a lot of noise behind you.
You're making it 50 feet or so, and then you hear...
rushing wave of things back as you guys are making your way through this tunnel.
We're going to go into sort of a bullet time run event, as you guys can do stuff.
You hear a lot of noises.
You are sprinting ahead.
Everybody go ahead and roll initiative.
And here's, and we'll, here's where we'll make it.
This will be with disadvantage, because I am exhausted.
Five.
That's pretty shitty.
I got four left.
It's okay.
Boom, boom.
Okay, what are the initiative rolls on this one?
Fifteen.
Six.
Five.
Is this what we're sticking the order?
Is you up front in second?
Yeah, I was sitting in the cave until you guys yelled at me, so definitely far point.
That makes sense.
At the very bottom, no matter what would be...
the lycanthropes of whatever kind um you guys i mean you guys are pretty seasoned fight at this point the amount of noise you hear behind you is concerning you're like oh shit um we're gonna get this there's no way we make it out of that fight alive so you're start running you get into a full sprint down this hallway um first up will be zario um we're gonna set a full distance is 350
tunnel space you don't know what's on the other side of it but you know that you have to get out of this space we're gonna say something happens on initiative count 20 at the new round and at the bottom of the round each time so you can use your full movement and dash you can use your movement and action to do something there we're gonna say no bonus actions at this point just for like this little mini thing we're doing here but sorry your first movement
Alright, just to see how it goes, I'm just going to run.
Do I have to roll anything?
Nope, just movement and dash?
Yeah, I'll do action and movement.
So you're still a bear?
I was thinking about that.
I'm faster as a bear, but I don't think I can fit.
You could fit as a bear, but nobody can pass you no matter what.
You take up the full space.
Yeah, I'll drop it.
Okay.
running on two feet as a bear anyway with your bowler hat.
Transition into your human form.
So that's 60 feet total.
Okay.
You're pretty fast walking on two feet as a bear.
Paladin, you're up.
I'm going to do the same thing.
I won't spend an action.
I'll use it to dash.
Okay.
So what's the full movement then?
60 feet.
Leopold, you are up.
So we're being pursued from behind, correct?
Yes.
The tunnel is six feet.
If you are having trouble standing full height, I'm not going to reduce your movement by any amount, but you don't have room to play around.
Okay.
I'm just going to use the grease spell to create difficult terrain.
Can I make that the whole surface of the tunnel?
Yeah.
As you're sprinting, you just like.
You're like sort of character running.
You go floor all the way around your body.
You sprint and you create a full arch of this sort of grease ball behind you.
Excellent.
So I'll do that with my action.
And then I'll use the remainder of my movement, which is 30 feet.
So I'll be behind you guys.
Because I use an action instead of dashing.
Okay.
and fill in the space you see dozens of like animalistic forms butting into each other shouldering running and filling and it's good thing you do what you do because you see some of them are like on the ceiling running towards you and then you see they're going much faster than you guys are currently and they sort of you're like 30 feet ahead at this point and then the grease hits them from behind and you see some of them trip and they sort of make a temporary blow
moving forward, but you see more animals come out of the tunnels behind them, sort of ahead of the block moving forward.
but they seem much faster than you guys at this point up at the top sorry yeah I'll use my action for movement again but then I'll tell Garfield to float to the back at the front of whoever's there and I want him to try to trip a big one
Okay, so he'll hang back.
Yeah, I want him to just, like, fall back and then, I don't know if it's an attack or what, but to try to block somehow.
Okay.
So if you float behind Leo and just move his movement to go opposite.
You guys are all technically moving forward at the same time, so the carpet will just stay and everybody sort of passes.
Leopold, as you're running forward, you see this little tabby cat that's just waiting patiently to sacrifice itself.
the tabby yeah um cal so 30 feet or 60 um i don't think there's anything i have that would be helpful um i'm too far away to do anything there yeah i don't have anything good so yeah i'll move um and then yeah you are at 120 caledon you are up
I'm going to use the cantrip firebolt to light the grease on fire.
Nice.
I'll move 30 more feet down the tunnel.
Make it to 90.
You turn your head and you shoot it and it lights it and you see you light the fur of enormous werewolves.
The bright eyes ignite and you see them
a mass of animals way more than you knew were in this tunnel system fighting and clawing and like reaching and like pushing each other back moving through this tunnel um i'm gonna say you have to move in for a second round on that um but you move 30 leo you are up
So I have Expeditious Retreat, but you said we're not doing bonus actions, so that doesn't really give me anything, right?
You could cast it as your action if you'd like.
But it just gives me the dash action.
Yeah.
The great thing about Expeditious Retreat is when you cast it, you can use it that round.
So I can say you can cast it and then get the dash as the action as part of that.
But then I wouldn't be able to dash additionally, right?
It would take the place of the dash.
Doesn't it also increase your movement at all?
It just says you take the dash action.
That's okay.
So you still have 30 feet of movement, right?
And then you still get the bonus 30.
But it doesn't... Because then the only other thing it lets me do is the dash action as a bonus action.
Correct.
So for the next coming rounds, while you hold that concentration...
I'll give you the extra move.
Okay, that's what I was asking, because we're not doing bonus actions.
No, like, you know, no constant, I'm going to throw firebolt stuff around, like, as extra stuff.
Minimize how much clutter we have in between these things.
Okay, yeah, yeah, so I will, I'll do an expeditious retreat to catch up, and I'll close that distance, I'll close 60 feet instead of 30.
Okay.
I guess the steel defender is...
Yeah, he's been moving, but he has movement speed of 40 feet, so he was...
Okay, I'll do that.
Yeah.
The tall boys are in the garage too, if you want some of those ones.
Oh man, I haven't had one of those in a while.
Instead of getting their 90, they'll go 45 with the addition of Garfield.
They're only gonna go 30, so they are at 60 at this point.
nice jonathan we got one of these garlic things too oh i love it great plate yeah it shreds just like the the roller too yeah i love the little skins off you guys got that at the farmer's market no my mom got it for christmas yeah i think i think megan's mom her parents got it for us and then travis had one too so i never had to use it so i pulled it out of my box and when we moved here i was like hell yeah that's a little brush you see um
You see this little tabby, he's standing essentially in the air with his arms out.
There is this mass of werewolves and he pushes one and he sticks his leg out and he's sort of like defending but all of a sudden you see just like multiple claws tear him into pieces as like he makes his one final stand as like the mass almost fills to the top of the tunnel space of like they can't crawl past each other before one finally pushes forward.
You see a werewolf topples ass over tea kettle out.
So back at the top is Ariel.
I think I'm just going to keep running.
I don't think I have anything else that I can do.
Move my dash?
Yeah.
Too far.
You make it to 180.
You are 120 feet from the open cavern space.
You can't see past it.
It's like it drops out.
You don't know if it's like a steep one or anything, but there's like a bigger space it opens out to.
Caledon.
I'm going to use move a hand.
You go 60, that puts you at 150.
Leopold so I'll do an action to dash and then with my expeditious retreat use a bonus action to dash so 30 60 90 yeah so you just kind of see me uh you already caught up to me Leopold gears are really spinning jump over in like more of your body and then tumble in front of Calvin as you pass him and you catch up to Zariel at the front um let's get out of here Calvin now in the back just barely by 30 feet um
At the very bottom, the werewolves move.
They have 90 feet, so they get to 150.
So they catch right up to Kaladin.
You see, as you are sprinting, sort of fast movement as you can, you see like this mass of creatures going up, and you're sort of like dodging hands and claws, and you're jumping, and then one will attack at you at disadvantage, which is right behind you.
Natural two misses.
Don't get clawed or anything.
Keep moving.
That's all they can do.
Top of the round, Zariel.
How far back was that?
They are 30 feet from the leaders.
They're 30 feet from us?
Yeah.
Jesus Christ.
I'm just 50 feet behind.
They have 90.
I'm just 30 feet behind.
Okay.
All right.
Let's see.
This is my original Mahart Village music.
Nice.
But since I was the only one listening to it, nobody else could hear it.
Oh, that's great.
You had your own soundtrack?
Yeah.
Oh, damn.
That's hilarious.
yeah yeah bernie have you ever been in the brewery where they have all of the jubilee posters yeah um like it's cool they change them out every year you see it goes all the way back to like yeah i mean i feel like it almost goes back to the 80s well i mean i think they i feel like they
so i'll burn another thing lost way where that i'll have it be six what did they start to sound like i don't know give me i mean i'm not gonna make you make a check you saw from what happened there are enough monsters behind you guys that it would not make it a full round before it got a mystery so at most you're gonna buy yourself having their action for one round kind of deal so if you want to waste disposal on that
I just don't have anything else I can do to slow it down at all.
How far away are we?
30 feet?
30 feet from the limit, you estimate you're about 120 from making it out.
And they have...
But we're even yeah Assuming I dash and dash Well, you've got 60 feet
Yeah, I'm going to burn the second level spell slot just to try to slow down a little bit.
I have up to 90% casting range.
It'll just appear right between Kaladin and them.
And I'm just gonna try to slow it down as much as I can.
What are you casting?
Sun and Beast.
Just something as big as it possibly can be.
As much space as possible.
And then you go 30.
Yeah, then I only go 30.
So that only puts me at like 210.
Kaladin.
With them essentially snapping at me and like right next to me, can I just reaction throw my hands up and cast...
Uh, the cantrip that we talked about.
Yeah.
It's a bonus action.
I'll cast as an action.
It does force damage.
So I'm just trying to maybe either collapse part of the tunnel or create difficult terrain.
Not necessarily target aware creature.
I like it.
Um, you're like getting snipped at and shoulders are like pushing your whole body.
And listen, you get one shove that almost turns you 180 degrees and you throw your hands up and shoot at the ground.
pushing yourself back.
Go ahead and, it'll just go off.
I'm gonna say there's, what is the damage die?
2d10.
There is a damage threshold of 15.
You break 15, the ground collapses.
Otherwise, you break difficult frames, you'll slow them down.
Okay.
I can't get there.
Eight.
Blows the ground, the ground sinks a little bit.
You see like one of the missteps, they sort of pile up again.
They'll have half movement for this round.
You push yourself a little bit, and then you continue to move at 30 more feet.
That puts you to 180 at that point, Leopold.
So he's made the tunnel a little unsturdy.
Yes.
So I have a spell Earth Trimmer, which generally I think is meant to just either cause difficult terrain or, you know, if a creature fails a deck save, it takes 1d6 bludgeoning.
But could I somehow focus it into the earth where he's made it unstable to try and collapse the tunnel fully?
You could try to do it at the top just to further create difficult terrain.
Yeah, essentially just like... Have their movement again.
Have it again.
Yeah, but that'll give you only... You'll only have a dash, so it'll be 60 feet opposed to 90 feet.
Yeah, yeah.
But you could do that.
I'll burn a spell, I'll cast Earth Trimmer, and I would get them down to, what, 30 feet?
45 half again, so they'd go... Oh, 22.
22, okay.
So you're making distance on them.
But that only lasts for one turn.
One round.
Is there running through it?
That's okay.
210, 240, 180.
They will...
I guess also we haven't discussed how your creature is gonna It did oh I see okay, so that was gonna slow down Okay After that goes to the werewolves turn you see a
into the ground and then like they hit that and they tumble over into Kaladin's sort of disturbed dirt that like their hands go into and like one of them snaps its shoulder and has like the other one step on it and like breaks it temporarily one of them is down and then like the ceiling collapses and like you just see temporarily it's just like a mound of dirt as you guys were sprinting and gaining distance before like the dirt explodes with other ones I mean just destroying the ones on the ground but they're now much farther behind
So they will only go 20 feet.
That puts them at 170 max.
Then back up to Katsuzara.
You're almost out.
Oh, just Action Dash.
That's all I got.
Takes you to 270.
You'll be out next turn with just Movement Paladin.
Same thing, Action Dash.
That takes you to...
I'm gonna action dash and then expeditious retreat for another dash 60 feet of your 90 feet movement you hit the edge of the tunnel you pass
step him too.
Give me a dexterity saving throw.
And that would be with disadvantage, correct?
No, it's a saving throw.
Okay, alright.
20, not 20.
22.
Love that.
I've got a map for it, but we're going to take a quick break.
Smoke a little bit for the big fight.
You...
hit this space and it is opening to this huge cavern but you've got so much momentum that you hit the ground you have like the foresight to be like there's a drop that you kick the wall as you go and you push yourself forward and you launch through this space and you land on top of this like dirt stone bridge that oversees like the area below it it's this huge cavern or space there are like elevated areas a platform that connects it in this huge bottom area underneath and you clearly
running into this open space too.
So it's a land bridge that connects.
Yeah.
What kind of gap did he clear?
Huge.
Okay.
Awesome.
There's some downfall to this too.
So I essentially jumped out of the tunnel and landed on an island that's elevated.
Is that what I'm picturing?
Yeah, I'll back it up.
From there, you jumped, cleared this whole space, and landed on top of it.
And landed perfectly in the middle.
Jesus.
That's when it gets you a lot.
You cleared this whole space, so they're going to be clearing out of here in a moment.
This, 60 feet up in the air, so you drop 60 feet down.
Yeah, I put them in my back, so...
That'll be your turn.
With it also a nat 20, I'm going to let you warn them that that's coming up.
As you, like, oh dear through the air, they know something is coming up.
Throw an oh dear out there.
They go... Like, oh, okay, all right, I better pay attention here.
Nobody has their movement this round, so they go the full 90, so that takes them to...
Right back to my ass.
Right up to Calvin.
Right up to my ass again.
That's a lot for all the stuff we've done slowing down.
It's okay.
At least we haven't been absolutely overwhelmed.
Sixes.
Yeah, that's great.
Love that.
Okay.
Back at the top.
So I heard him yell, oh dear.
Yes.
You didn't hear just that.
You heard, oh dear.
We've got a telepathic bond.
I'll move.
Jump.
That's when you fucking leave the tunnel.
As I get to the edge, is it, uh, is it, like, a cliff, or is there, like...
It's a 60-foot drop.
Just a sheer, like... Yeah.
Drops down.
Like, the tunnel lets out, we'll say, like, technically right here, because I don't want to be like, oh, I just jumped there.
You guys don't have, like...
You with the action could do something to get yourself to this point.
You could get to like a platform or something or to here.
Leopold fucking cleared this enormous amount of space.
Whichever one is the closest, can I try to make a jump?
Yeah, so you can do a dexterity saving throw with advantage.
11.
And that's a 20.
Excellent.
So Ariel jumps out and then as he's partway through the air, just like double jump, fine whips to there and catches his shoulder and you see just all the way, hits that, slides onto his feet.
No issue there.
Since you were out of the chase sequence, you also have your bonus action if you can do anything with the bonus.
Nothing good.
and your turn.
Yours is full movement and dash.
Does that get me to the edge?
It gets you to the edge.
You are 240, 60 feet, takes you to the 300 mark.
Yeah, same thing.
But you won't have something fun, just dexterity things are with advantage to do something.
That's a 17 plus 4.
Let's do it.
21.
Left or right?
If I make a big gap, I'll
I'll go right.
We'll split the difference.
You sort of see that Zario goes left and you sort of angle it on the tunnel where you're kind of wall running a little bit and then you leap out to the right and catch just the edge of
sweet onto your feet and then we'll get to what you oh you see as you guys like clear that just a massive like like it just pour out of the tunnel space just ass over tea kettle falling into the space below some of them hit the ground like you hear like the yelps is like they die from like they've been pummeled and stepped on sometimes some of them like run to try to catch up and like scratch to climb the walls and you hear this
large deep sort of growling howl and all of them sort of stop and they back up and they sort of hit on the perimeter just
piercing yellow eyes as a creature comes into view but we'll take a quick break put a beanie baby
Is this space, is this also a pit?
This is 60 feet down.
So this is traversable.
And we're elevated.
This is like tunnels in between.
Okay.
We'll say this is like maybe 10, 15 feet wide.
So 45 feet of movement space.
These are all, anything colored is 60 feet elevated.
So is he standing on like the edge of a...
He's technically on another piece of like this that's just like where he was laying.
All right.
How large is this creature?
Huge, huge, huge.
We're mediums.
Large, huge, gigantic.
Okay.
He could clear these tunnels.
What is the largest creature called?
Colossal.
Okay, so on the scale of how big he could be.
It's triple our size.
Right.
he could make it through this tunnel so he could he couldn't probably make it to the one we were running at all yeah six feet but underneath this little land bridge yeah this is six feet yeah he is a 20 foot creature yeah okay right 20 isn't that when huge starts yeah something like that okay um um you guys uh in this space
you see this enormous werewolf, fully, you see it's got long limbs and fairly muscular legs, and it's not just on four feet, it seems to be almost bipedal, using the other ones to sort of guide its movements.
Somewhere between, well, it's not fully standing like a bear.
It's somewhere like it pushes itself onto two feet, but can definitely walk if it wanted to, but usually probably crawls.
In dead space, piercing yellow, red eyes,
And it very much is familiar to you guys.
You saw a creature that very much looked just like this on the attack on that festival.
It lets out its enormous howl as you guys can just go ahead and roll initiative again, you know?
Get right into it.
I have a quick question.
Yes.
I rolled a dirty 20-hour initiative.
Okay.
the shield does it have is it a regular shield or is it like a plus one shield 14 regular shield it just does additional things if it's against a creature do what I can 10 it's better I think that's the best roll I've had all night for advantage yeah alright
What happens to the creature that I bought before?
Is it a disadvantage to hit me, or is it, like, advantage, or how does that work?
You would have to set it up, so you can try to set it up real quick.
You attempt to recount past battles, both real or imagined, to the shield upon a successful DC and charisma persuasion, or 15 charisma deception check.
You gain a plus one bonus.
The creatures described will hold in the shield.
So a plus one.
You had a real fight.
It shouldn't be too hard.
I was going to say, yeah.
Get this added in.
Not one that's that big.
It doesn't matter.
It's a truth.
It's a plus two shield.
And then a plus three.
Against that creature.
If it's successful.
You had your action.
He's got a 17.
Oh, when I got here.
level crazy all right so i'll just look at the shield i'll take it i was just thinking like that i'd be like i'll be like well uh i just want to play games i play with bunnies
My charisma is a minus one.
I like how you had a very personal conversation with the shield.
Alright.
No, I go with a five.
It's like... Bullshit.
Very faintly dog-faced.
Like, not convincing enough that it forms.
You see, like, the metal is just perfectly mirror-finished.
Like, it just down rough shapes of what you're trying to count it as.
Yeah, there's a really cool shield that's an exit.
No, I'm like shaking it.
Okay, well, that's my action.
There's only how many uses of that?
I can only fail three times.
And then just trick it three times.
Three attempts just, three failed attempts just wipe it clean.
It doesn't destroy it.
Oh, okay.
No, that's against all the creatures you've actually got in there.
No, like, yeah, total of three failed attempts.
and then it resets but you can keep telling it more stories again to get back up to those same is it a count if it's a truth that you just yeah don't lower check okay but if you fail that still counts to three good enough story yeah so that was my previous action so
Yeah, I'm pretty sure it was a three, too.
Yeah.
I was gonna say a two, but...
I don't know, I don't know.
To the benefit of the doubt.
We want to be fair.
Yeah, we don't want to cut him short.
25 to 20?
20.
20 to 15?
19.
Jeez, you guys.
10... 15 to 10?
10.
Highest yet.
What's your dex bonus?
Mine?
Yeah.
Yeah, plus two.
Yeah, the big guy's probably not super dexterous.
I don't see any reason to get closer.
I'm gonna go ahead and I'm gonna bring up a call of lightning.
I'm gonna reach to the top.
How tall is this space?
80, 90 feet.
All right, so I'll go to about 60 feet from the cavern, right about here in the center, and a big dark storm cloud is gonna appear.
Lightning's gonna begin to shoot out of it, and then it's gonna shoot a bolt right down at this guy.
He's gonna need to make a DC,
half of 3D10.
If you want to make it easier, you can just say he fails.
I was just trying to see if I could connect my... Oh, DC 15 deaths.
Jess, you crack me up with that shit.
You know, you just want to...
It's a natural two.
There you go.
All right.
It's a 3d10.
Lightning damage.
One.
Oh, what level is this spell?
Level three.
He gets advantage.
Oh, don't do me like that.
Lesser magic resistance.
It gets advantage on saving throws to resist effects of spells cast at third level or lower.
Ooh.
It's going to be crucial.
Well, that changes what I might have done.
Fourteen.
Failure.
Okay, all right.
So it was a one, then it was a nine.
I'm good for that.
So ten, and then three.
13 lightning damage.
Doesn't he get stunned though?
Or that was only the toad for some reason.
Yeah.
Let's see, that's Concentration, and then I'm going to use... No, that's an action.
Okay, that's my turn.
I will just...maybe I'll move to
um this space i'm gonna call 60. this is farther so we'll say from this point here we'll call that 80. and then obviously i said this was 60 feet tall so you don't do that again
Um, I'm going to go ahead and cast mirror image on myself.
And I'll move 30 feet.
I'm going to, I'm assuming this is, I can just keep spurting the
learn about an early old how and it will just um uh this is leopold right leopold no i'm not this is leopold oh sorry there's ariel yeah zario and uh kaladin go ahead and give me
constitution saving throws you guys are close enough to the walls that all of those sort of lycanthropes and wolves that have been sort of subdued by its presence uh at this moment all are like coordinated to reach out and bite at you as you were running by you're just close enough are there so they're like little holes they're popping out they're popping out and getting yeah so you guys both get bit but this is rats wait so is it for damage or is it for
you should do it again just to see 19 it's a con
that was just from the walls that was like yeah because i'm running around the edge yeah there are apparently like small holes oh the claws it's almost like a dad so should i assume i'll assume that even though i was bitten uh didn't like get purchased the whole thing was like fail both something that
Succeed on the first one, you're fine.
Succeed on the second one, you're fine.
It's a double negative.
That's what I'm just getting for not rolling hits.
It'll be its turn.
On its turn, it can do a couple things.
It'll use its Frightful Presence.
Any creature it can see within 120 feet must make a DC 18 Wisdom Saber be frightened for one minute.
That might be around the edge.
60, we'll call it 10, so 70.
And then...
What was it?
60.
I think you're right there.
Oh, I'm definitely.
Yeah.
Wastem save.
That's a strong one for you.
14.
Fail.
This is a flat.
15.
15 fail.
Roll it again.
Oh, I guess it doesn't matter.
It's because you failed.
So roll it again.
Oh, I thought the for saving throws.
You are frightened.
Or do I?
Oh, it's just a check.
make it again so 15 i'm frightened yes both of you are frightened until you succeed you can repeat the save at the end of each of your turns and once you succeed you don't get it doesn't happen again right means they can't move towards you cannot attack towards it and attack it with disadvantage uh one round one uh one minute okay so make that save yeah it's got 60 feet of movement so it will just
leap no right to here standing leap 60 feet it's 20 feet tall on the uh on the bridge bridge you see it like its leg will just get out and like uh throw itself into the air and sort of like picks itself up gets it down take two attacks on leopold good luck you're ready to get that shield out i have one more
You've got to be a little more reserved.
I was burning a lot to get us out of that cave.
That was the top part.
Dirty 20 misses, correct?
Yes.
Jeez.
It's got to be a 21.
It's so hard to hit.
It's just straight up.
You still have to land it, don't worry.
16 plus 9.
25.
25, I will shield.
And that gets you to it?
26, right, because it's a plus 5.
That is so hard.
It goes to bite and you just like, the metal dinks and dents and then it lets go and backs up.
It's not used to not biting something with meat.
For a lair action?
Yeah.
Or legendary or whatever that was.
Yeah, I wasn't going to deal with that.
For my turn... Oh, Jesus.
I got a laser sword.
Yeah, sure.
Let's see what it does.
Yeah, so while I have disadvantage because I'm frightened, do I also have double disadvantage?
No, it doesn't stack.
No, it doesn't stack, which is why this is not always advantageous.
If he had advantage from something and then had disadvantage, he couldn't give himself advantage a different way to get advantage.
It would just be a zero.
Single disadvantage no matter what.
All right, so with disadvantage... You wouldn't be disadvantaged otherwise.
I have one point of exhaustion, right?
Yeah, but that's not an attack.
It's a ability check.
Oh, excellent.
Well, in that case...
He's frightened right now.
He does have a disadvantage.
Yeah, all right.
I thought I would have had double because... Yeah, that was my question.
Got it.
But because I'm frightened...
Yeah, 7 plus 9, I don't think it's going to make contact there.
16?
16 misses, great.
And that will be my action and my bonus action.
I think I had one stone that I haven't thrown yet floating around.
So with my bonus action, I will hurdle a stone.
Disadvantage.
Fuck.
Natural one.
Are you going to hit me with it?
No, you're far enough away.
You're far enough away.
I think it just goes wide.
Yeah, it does go wide.
Into the pit of rare creatures.
It just hits its leg because there's not enough space for it to get any momentum and it falls to the ground.
You see, like, it hits the ground and, like, a werewolf runs out of the shadows, grabs it, and, like, just, like, like a ball.
I thought it was a ball.
Like that 50 cent opening pitch.
Yeah.
Oh, it's its last one.
So its shield lasts for my...
Doesn't it?
Don't worry about it.
Okay.
But I guess if it does, how long does a shield last?
Until the start of your next turn.
Okay, so basically any attacks would be.
Yes.
It's a nice one for the whole round.
Oh, me?
Yes, do you want?
Oh.
I'm still afraid.
Unless you're Eminem.
So... No, good one.
Singer.
Hey.
You're in my house.
I was going to let it go, but I heard somebody say, that was good.
That was great.
He could tell.
Okay.
Oh, shit.
This is an action.
I'm just going to burn another action to have the lightning bolt hit again.
That's going to be it.
All right.
Okay, I was going to say, I hear the Zelda.
That was really weird.
How much?
Fifteen and a half to seven.
And then I'll use my bonus action to do nothing because I don't have any bonus actions.
Okay.
Up next.
Is it an action?
I wonder what the next Zelda game will be.
Yes.
Okay.
I'll probably pull one out soon, right?
They just made a, like, a kid's version.
It's all princess stuff, though.
She's Peach.
It's not Peach.
Zelda.
It would be Zelda, yeah.
Interesting.
But it's a cartoon?
Every other game, they kind of switch off.
We just didn't know if it could.
uh i feel like it's got to be time for a new super smash too it's been years since they put one out if i use my
I use my 30 feet of movement.
This is easily within the 60.
Yeah, 60 feet's about my pencil, so.
Am I at 60 feet right now?
Pretty close.
No.
Oh.
Okay, but if I move.
If you moved a little bit forward, you would be.
All right, I took my whole 30 feet to here.
Yes.
Okay.
Oh, I didn't roll for saving fear.
Go for it.
Oh, neither did I, actually.
But then I would have disadvantage because this is a check.
No, it's a save.
Okay, got it.
That's confusing that a lot of me.
Eleven.
In combat, it's almost never going to be relevant unless it's a strength contested strength.
Ah, okay.
So that's a good way to remember it.
Okay.
So if we're in combat, it'll almost never be relevant.
Yeah, that's good.
What's the cavern height here?
80 feet?
And so anti-grav literally just flips the gravity.
Just floats it.
Use the action to throw the sphere up to 60 feet where it shatters and casts levitate on all creatures.
Spell safe DC 15.
An object within 15 foot radius lasting for one minute.
No concentration required.
levitate is you don't go up you just stop moving where you are and you can't unless you get like telepathically fly space restraint pretty much yeah we've got them restrained within a space it can move but like if it jumped into the air it would just keep going that way because it can't control its space so it does
It would be like an air hockey puck.
You can just push in a way and it can't stop itself.
In theory.
There'd be some checks to be made.
Would you throw it?
I'd throw it.
It's got to make a dex save, it looks like.
No, no, no, a strength.
Actually, I don't know.
I just said it's a DC 15.
I said it's a DC 15 right now.
That's just what I wrote down from the session because we didn't have the object check.
Okay.
No, wouldn't be right.
Getting affected?
No, because Charisma affects...
It's a constitution saving card.
It is a constitution saving card.
Unwilling creature must succeed a constitution saving card.
I figured it would have been like a Strength check.
My thought, yeah, if it was Reverse Gravity, I would have thought Strength to Dex, but since it's just Levitate, it's just an effect that happens.
Because you're just trying to resist it?
Yeah, I guess because you can save against it and then nothing happens versus Reverse Gravity where everything flips.
Because Levitate is a second level spell, so it'll get advantage.
Oh, and it's...
I like this cow.
16 and 18, I'm gonna die.
That's tough, this guy is...
So that just negated... Can the orb hit him to give him damage?
No.
It's just, like, knocked to the head.
Leopold also must have succeeded the con save.
So if you succeed the con save, then it'll give him, like, damage?
1d4, sure.
What am I rolling here?
A con city.
I got a decently high con.
16, yeah 22.
Okay, roll 1d4 damage.
Roll that damage.
4.
3.
Alright.
That's Sam Pringle style rolling right there.
You see a couple of slashes in its body sort of close and heal up a little bit.
This guy's healing.
Yeah, we didn't really do that.
I guess we had no time, we just took off.
It started its turn, it recharges its bite.
But it will use its Frightful Presence again.
So you have already succeeded.
I'm still frightened.
Still frightened, but it doesn't affect you again.
You need to take it now.
What is the save this time?
It's a DC 18 Wisdom save.
So once you succeed, it can't affect you again?
Yeah.
For the fight?
24 hours for the game, but for all intents and purposes.
You're like, I already saw you, buddy.
I already know.
I know what you do.
That's pretty neat.
My shield's scary.
Would you call it an 18?
18.
Got it.
Nice.
Yeah, my wisdom is fried.
I have proficiency in that.
I chose that as one of the beats as I give me just that save because my modifier is so soft.
I think I did 21, well, has it been the start of my turn?
So 26 is the AC.
At the end of its turn, it'll use two legendary actions to bite you.
To me?
Yeah.
17 plus nine, 26.
26 hits.
Beats it first to break that barrier.
That's a high roll.
I know, man, that really is.
It's really hard to hit you.
Yeah, plus nine is tough.
You guys have plus nine to hit.
We're only level six, and you've got a plus eight on your modifier for your... Yeah, that's wild.
That's god rolled order.
Yeah.
You take 13 piercing damage and give me a constitution saving throw.
Okay.
13 damage.
Don't worry, if you catch the curse, they won't hurt you.
They haven't hurt me since I got turned, so...
So I hear, that's...
The empirical evidence is talented.
Uh...
12.
Fail.
Can you turn a suit of armor into a were-creature?
You don't have blood, technically correct.
No.
So you will not be cursed unless you want to be, technically you would be.
But you still take 86 necrotic damage.
86.
That's a lot of ones.
It's okay, middle of the row, he's got some 3Ds in there, that's not bad.
31 is an average.
So you take that.
I'm not going to take another one like that.
None of us can.
I can take one of those, two of those.
And then that's the end of legendary action.
Next up is Leopold.
Oh, man.
This is good cow fighting music.
Thanks.
It's a were-cow.
Thank you very much.
Let's see, Burning Hands is just touch, so it's not like a roll to hit.
Well, it is, but you have to be able to touch.
Yeah, you can't be five feet away.
Yeah, I'm, right?
You're there, you're working.
But I'm not going to roll to hit something.
They're just going to have to pass a dex save.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Yeah, I will cast Burning Hands at the second level.
Okay.
It's a deck save.
15 foot cone.
When I cast it at the second level or higher, the damage increases by 1d6 for each level above the first.
Yeah, it's a 16, so they save.
That would be, yeah, half damage.
And 3d6.
And since I did it at the second level, it would be 4d6, but halved.
Okay.
Here's 3.
4, 8, 10, and... 2.
12, so 6 damage.
um for sure how much damage six six is that half yeah that was already half so it was 12 initially my bonus action i will bring up another magic stone and that will be uh that'll be my turn okay we gotta we gotta figure out how to hit this guy with some silver after your turn all these
It's last legendary action to make another claw attack at you.
But you see that you threw the fire at it and sort of up into its face and it makes this attack not looking at you and swipes sort of wildly.
I was also going to roll to get rid of the fear.
Go ahead.
17.
12 to hit.
12 does not hit.
Uh, 17 on the... Oh!
Really?
DC 18 safe.
Oh god, I have a flat roll, so that's... Yeah, we're gonna need to help you.
That's impossible.
Uh, it's claw attack is a nat 20 and a 3.
Yeah.
And it has to roll disadvantage, and it took the fire damage.
Yeah, that's why I was like, oof.
Keepin' in with fire.
Yep.
Roger.
At the start of the round.
Thoroughly, you are up.
Think about dropping this thing.
It's just not doing much damage.
I'm going to have to do something like that.
I'm going to drop it.
I'm going to move in.
I'm going to use my action to transfer to my bear form.
Bonus action.
Beforehand, I'm going to bring out my flaming claws.
So, hat on, claws out.
What a statement.
Let's see here.
That's all I can do.
I'll move in, though, to harry him.
That way he can get some... You're going to get up his ass.
I'm going to be snipping.
See what I can do.
You can't attack him, though?
That was the action and bonus just to get their spells and stuff.
At the start of the round, it should have been the werewolves on the walls.
Go ahead and give me a dexterity saving throw.
Should I have one too?
No, you moved away.
That's a 14 on the dex.
Give me a common save.
We're all going to be fucking werewolves.
I was going to say, it's just lesser restoration.
No difference.
You don't feel like you got it.
I do like the idea of transforming into a metal werewolf.
I'm going to use...
Right now, having been in the tunnel and sort of realizing that what felt very intuitive, like very protective whenever those blasts came out of my hands, I'm going to do the same thing again.
I'm going to raise my hand and cast the Esoptric Blast.
Nice.
That'll be a 23 to hit.
Yes.
And a natural one.
Nine.
I'm going to close.
Can I move 30 feet forward?
Yeah.
Will that put me... That's not going to quite get me.
I'll be like here.
Okay.
I'm going to use a feature from light splitter.
The arc.
One where it's like two things just like fly out of the light splitter.
Yeah, arc slash gives me a ranged attack now.
Do I still use my weapon modifier, my dex modifier for that?
It's just a normal attack, you can do any difference.
Okay, okay.
You can only use it once.
You can only activate it once.
Right, right, right.
That'll be a...
Does that do any elemental?
No, it just gives me one-time ranged weapon attack.
Oh, nice.
But that's nice.
That hits for a max damage.
You always get the addition of like the radiant or a product on the bonus.
Oh, what are you doing radiant?
So that was 10 14 19.
Yeah Nice no, no, no my pluses are 317 Good round next up will be its turn.
It's not quite
We're looking right now.
Yeah, he's dinged up.
But he's still in the fight.
He's going to shove and attack you off the side.
This is a little bit of a strength check.
Batting you like a cat toy.
Oh, this is where the exhaustion would come into play.
This is a check.
Strength check.
Yeah, I'm not gonna win that.
Five.
A 25.
It doesn't do any damage on the attack itself, but if you get this way, you will fall 60 feet on your turn and hit the ground.
unless you have a way to change that.
But you are currently falling, and it'll use its second attack.
I can use my reaction to cast Feather Fall.
Okay.
Feather Fall is on seven.
Yeah, she's up to you and five creatures.
What's the range?
I'm a creature.
60 feet.
Nice, okay.
That's why it's a good reaction.
Oh, it's a fantastic reaction.
I was going to say, I was going to have to work with something else.
Okay.
I have one ace in my pocket for that.
I was thinking you could shoot your steel defender straight down and have it rocket you back down.
Just a little bit.
Sorry, so you cast Feather Fall.
Yep.
So he's going to fall at a normal pace, half speed, so you'll still be in the air.
It does say that I can choose to cast it on me or up to five people within range.
So can I go ahead and hit us all with it and hold concentration in case we get thrown?
Feather Fall ends once you hit the ground.
Okay.
So you guys being on the ground, you'd instantly be lost on you.
So you could cast it on yourselves, but... Oh, I see what you're saying.
Okay.
It's really at that thick for now.
Perfect, okay, perfect.
so she's just the one effect, because I've got no level ones anymore.
Does that basically mean I don't take any damage?
It'll move forward to close the distance with Kaladin, so you didn't attack him opportunity.
Okay, so what did we decide with the bear?
If I cast a one attack, because that's what the weapon thing is, and you said the bonus was about the same anyway.
Yeah.
Well, so if I do a regular attack as a bear...
I do way more damage than with the thing, so can I just add a little bit of fire to my regular attacks instead?
Just do it that way?
No.
No?
That's not what we agree on.
Well, then I'm just not going to cast that.
But the fire gives it disadvantage on its next attack.
So there is a benefit to this.
Yeah, I guess that's fair.
Okay, how much is it?
Okay, so... 18 to hit you.
Let's see.
Mind attack.
Shield.
No, no, no.
I've got your image.
Let me see if it hits one of them.
Oh, yeah.
Natural one.
Okay, two.
It's me.
Shield.
Actually, it's a dirty point.
Because this creature is large.
So that's going to be 3d6 fire damage.
3, 4, so 7.
12 fire damage.
As I...
Right across its booty.
And then with Sentinel... That would be great.
That would be cool.
Okay.
Uh...
It missed you.
And that was its turn.
Let's see if it got hit.
It does not get its breath weapon back.
Sweet.
It doesn't get its bite back.
Breath weapon, I was going to say.
Lightning breath.
Yeah, yeah.
Just start spraying lightning breath.
Good.
Oh, were-dragon would be fucking nuts.
Leopold, your turn.
You were falling.
You fall half speed, I believe, so you will make it halfway to the ground on your turn, but you have full control of your body.
You're not falling with imminent danger.
If I land on the ground, I won't take damage at half speed?
You won't take damage, but you won't hit the ground on your turn either.
Okay.
for your turn okay and i still have a little bit of sight onto this creature up here yes it's 60 feet up but it's like you can see like the top half of his shoulder dude i have had to have absolutely i guess i guess i have one option to get out of that hole i have no idea i'm just gonna have a fun time down there um
There's many of the smaller werewolves in the base of this pit.
Yeah, so you hit your turn, you start by the end of it, you hit the compactizer going down, you see they're just lined all the way around the perimeter, watching and waiting patiently for something to fall into the pit.
Right, great.
They're probably going to be nice.
Yeah, I was thinking that too.
Probably just a car wash. Um...
Firebolt?
Is that a cantrip you have?
Yeah, I was thinking about that, but if I'm...
If I'm stuck in a pit with thousands of little creatures that are going to tear me up...
I don't know what your AoE effect is going to be, so that's going to blast them all away from you.
I don't have anything.
I mean, I have Thunder Wave, but...
I don't think that would even really... No, just a 45 degree angle in front of you.
That's all you're protecting.
How much death points does...
He's ready for another one.
I was going to say, I haven't had many.
Give him two.
Yeah.
Take him to the edge.
For the greater good.
I was trying to track my...
I think I only have two, but... Yeah, two.
Okay, what I will do...
Oh, did I miss one?
Because I thought I added it.
You all had one pretty early on, and then you went the longest with that one, but you did use one to heal somebody.
Oh, I did?
So that was the second one.
Okay.
And he touched the beam.
So three, yeah.
Yeah, because the beam saw I got my fourth.
Let me add one there.
Remember, you can heal people with your own hit.
I'm gonna scream pocket sand and I'm just gonna start spraying fog out of my cufflinks and disappear I'm casting fog cloud at the second level
I'm disappearing into a cloud of fog.
No one sees me.
It says, uh...
You create a 20-foot radius sphere of fog centered on a point within range.
That point is directly on me.
The sphere is heavily obscured.
So presumably these creatures can't see me?
And with that, I'm going to try and climb out of the fucking pit.
Cause I'm like right here next to the wall somewhere.
I think you're through your right down.
Right down here.
You got to move to the wall first.
So you got about, you got 20 or like a, is this call?
There's a, there's a call up there.
Yes.
I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to start trying to climb that column.
That's good.
You got, you got at least.
Uh, 18.
You start moving up the wall.
You can do it.
I'm going to reset this.
At the start of the round, because you are in the pit still, you see one wolf sort of walk south starling.
I'm heavily obscured.
I can't see anything.
Right, okay.
Fair point.
I don't know where you are.
They can't see me.
Don't tell me what happens.
Just make it happen.
Okay.
Ankles are getting big.
It means hearing and smell.
It means smell for the rotisserie.
I would have never seen that.
It just doesn't smell right.
That's a seven.
It only just barely knows where you are.
God damn it, that fucking chip.
I hawk it out of my chest cavity and curl it off.
Give me a constitution saving throw.
Jesus.
Ten.
Ten, give me a constitution saving throw.
That's a little higher.
But I'm already cursed.
No, you're not cursed.
You decided that you couldn't.
Okay.
Yeah, that'll be 15.
15 passes.
Yeah.
I think it's like a 12.
It's not as good as his.
His is different.
How did he see me?
That's like, you're climbing up this obscured area, you can barely, you're just like reaching up blindly, you see like this just mouth and jaw and teeth just up in the smoke, grabs your foot, falls down, disappears from the smoke, as you hear the snarling up at the very top of Nazario.
I'm gonna move into this guy's space here.
I'm gonna make my attack to his advantage.
That's all I have.
He hasn't been using his reaction, so that's gonna be good.
Yeah, oh, 13 actually.
Does 13 make a difference?
That's a lot.
Okay.
Uh, how am I doing?
Yeah.
Um...
He's already been hit with fire right now, right?
So his next attacks... Not on misty ground.
Okay.
I'll misty step backwards.
So not that I'm so close to the wall to trigger that effect, but to back up.
Okay.
I'll cast Firebolt.
With a pin into this, it's like a fruit.
This is.
Cool, cool, cool.
That was bonus action and action.
Yeah, that's how I feel.
Just trying to set that up so it wouldn't be so bad.
Yeah, it's all right.
I'm the only one he can hit right now, so it'll be all right.
I'm already cursed too, so it's really best case scenario.
I was going to ask, is talking to S.H.I.E.L.D.
a bonus action or an action?
Action.
I have no good bonus action.
Hey, remember that one fight?
Hey, help me out here, man.
Start of the wolf's turn does not get its bite back.
You see clumsily, turns, almost slipping, back to face you, and it'll pick.
15 to hit.
First one hits.
Oh wait, no, I'm a bear.
Sorry, sorry.
It's okay, you still got hit points.
More points than I got.
Uh, 9 slashing damage, and then... We don't need all those.
12 points of necrotic damage.
You are considered staggered for this round.
Just being a bear, having to do that.
When staggered, a character has disadvantage on attack rolls and spell saves.
Oh, and Spell Sinks have a 25% chance to fail.
Spells, not Spell Sinks.
Interesting.
I've never seen a standard before.
Yeah, me neither.
I've never heard of that.
Oh, Jonathan, speaking of effects, can I roll for the frame?
Yes.
14.
Yeah.
No, it's flat roll.
I would be moving closer by climbing up the... God damn it.
I'm just hiding in this cloud.
I can't find it.
It's like a quiet place.
Just don't move.
Or have, you know, a chicken in your chest cavity.
You take 11 slashing and then another con save because it hit you both times.
It hit me again?
Well, it hit you with both the caps, right?
Oh, yeah, because I'm up here.
So I need another con save.
Oh, I thought those two were the damage, right?
Shit, I might not be careful.
19, 20, and 2.
Oh, that succeeds.
So you take half damage.
So it was 8, 10, 11, after 5.
So it was 11 for the first and then 5 for the second.
I'm doing absolutely fine.
Okay.
End of your turn.
End of its turn.
It'll use a legendary action.
I guess.
Might as well.
Um.
Put that little hat in front of its claw.
I think I'm trying to and it's just watching right through it.
13-1.
Take a duck.
Top of the round.
It'll be the initiative 20 thing.
How is this creature looking?
I think I've hit it once or twice.
Yeah, I probably hit about 10.
I can't even get any closer to it.
18.
Well, that's plus 220.
Was that for fear?
What was that?
I think that was... By a random werewolf that could have found me in the smoke?
Just passes through, gets you.
Dario, your turn.
Alright, so I'm not a bear.
So I can do anything.
I still have...
Yeah, I'm not doing well.
I only have one more spell slot.
I have one second level spell slot.
This is where...
But I mean... Well, it's still got Flame Blade up.
I need a couple more because I'm multiclass.
Like, as soon as I've got two attacks, I'm a fighter.
Yeah, that'll be next level.
We'll start over now.
We got this.
I'm not worried one bit.
We got so many syringes now.
So yeah, I'll attack him with the flame blade.
He's got a lot.
I'll have you guys take a check in a moment.
And he's healing.
I'm not flanking.
I'm not hearing.
Let's see.
He's been healing, remember?
I'll still try to hit him.
That's why I tried to hit him with fire.
Does the fire prevent him from healing?
I guess it just gives him disadvantage.
I got this.
Seven fire damage.
The fire helps a lot, but I don't know if it helps.
Gives it disadvantage on its next attack.
Everybody go ahead and give me a perception or insight check.
solidly zeros.
Doesn't matter which one.
14?
24.
I see something.
25.
The fire is definitely like it's afraid of the fire to some extent where it gets a little hesitant after each fire attack.
You notice that it's regularly healing a significant portion with your guys' attack, even magical.
So we probably need to get the silver.
No, I got this.
We seem to get it.
Oh, hey guys, what's going on up there?
You can't see because it falls out.
And then, Cali, your turn.
I'm going to cast Toll the Dead.
Nice.
Radio Wisdom saving throw.
Well, that is a what level spell?
It's a cantrip, so he'll have advantage.
So it's gonna be a 2d 12 and he can't heal That's a toll the dead thing for a cantrip Like ice.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's a product.
I will read it to you and I'll let you judge it to see which takes precedence The blank werewolf.
I'm gonna tell you that regenerates 20 HP at the top
Oh, did they change the rules on this one?
You can use both.
If you check the old one, it's one of the spells you can change out for if you'd like.
Oh, that's terrible.
Did they make this new?
Oh, because did they release an update?
The updated book has different spells effects.
Oh shit.
It changes things very subtly.
The monk is the most different.
They're not even called key points anymore.
Okay.
Do they get better?
They have some death drawbacks.
I feel like Amonk was kind of tough sometimes.
You're like, god damn it.
Yeah, so in the Legacy one, I feel like they're not allowed to regenerate.
I know that was Chill Touch, but what is that?
Oh, is that Chill Touch?
That's what I'm thinking of.
Oh, you told the dead?
I told the dead.
Oh, yeah, I touched it.
So they have to be damaged by Silver Weapon.
I was thinking Chill Touch.
Which we don't have.
They can't regenerate.
Yeah, we need to... Because we didn't prepare.
Yeah, I like that the one piece of advice that we were given was, use silver.
Google says that chill touch would bypass the healing though.
It would take press of covering, so...
have a way to stop it from healing that's good so I was looking at my equipment and for something silver and in my inventory once you showed me how to make things in my own inventory I wrote long dong silver what is that it's like long
Craig's over there sitting in the corner.
Ah, yeah.
Ah, yeah, that's what I'm here for.
I don't know what that is.
I didn't talk to you, but I just made it because I thought it was funny.
So out of my bag, I pull.
I pull out, yeah.
That was action or bonus action?
That was action.
That was...
Okay.
Next is...
Sorry guys, I had the wrong spell in my head.
The wolf.
That's alright.
Does it get its spikes?
It does not.
It will take attacks on Zariel.
So it's right there.
Bring it on.
This thing's probably healed more than we have damage to.
First one is a...
shield, it brought me to a 19, and since this thing's big, I'm at a 20.
Nice.
Why do you have a buff to things that are large?
Because of the ring.
Oh, your giant slayer ring.
Nice.
I also have a plus one to hit
9 plus 5, 14 points of slashing damage.
But it doesn't, I'm going to say it doesn't do the necrotic thing when it's not at its turn.
Leopold, bottom of the pit.
Bottom of the pit, can't go up.
uh you should just spin yourself so you don't know which direction you're going and then just move your yeah because even if you're frightened you know you're just moving forward yeah yeah
i'm not frightened of the fog in front of me so you could like make a run and jump for above the wolves on like the wall and try to climb farther away from it yeah so the fog was a 20 foot radius i guess so my pencil is 60 so we'll say a third of it the fog gets about to the wall okay so i'd be obscured yes up until then uh yeah i'll go i'll go that direction
And I'll start climbing.
Do you want to jump before you get to the wall?
Yeah, try to give me a little height.
So you don't run into a wolf?
Oh yeah, for sure.
And, uh...
I guess as my action or bonus action, I've got some climbing pitons.
You can just climb without those, but give me an athletics check.
I can't start throwing those in the wall.
You know, just give me a little bit so I won't fall down.
You're not even using a hammer.
You're just, you know, just like.
Athletics check.
All right.
So something to give me a little bit with disadvantage.
Okay.
Yeah.
All right.
That would be 10.
You can start putting some pitons in, but you'll move half pace.
Okay.
I've got a little hammer that I'm... You're technically only five feet up on the wall, so you're like standing on a wolf to do this.
They're just gnawing at your lower half.
I'm sinking some handholds in there.
So I'm going to move half speed.
Can I use my action to dash then?
Yeah.
Okay, so I'll move 30 feet, so I'm halfway up the wall.
I guess I'm now no longer obscured.
Not if you're 25 feet from the top of the wall.
And the wolves down below me are stuck in that fog, circling.
End of the round.
Nobody is close enough to get fit.
Top of the round, Zario.
I'm close enough to get fit.
No, the player action, the walls.
Oh, oh, gotcha, gotcha.
Uh, yeah.
Okay.
I was so excited about that cantrip, guys.
Yeah.
Oh!
It looked like you had my number.
I've used that to, like, essentially take down, like, ice giants and shit.
Because that Australians will regenerate.
And so it's like an overpowered cantrip in certain situations where it just takes away.
They can't regen.
They can't get hit points back.
Yeah, I mean.
I usually switch out Chill Touch and Shocking Grass.
All right.
Shocking Grass.
I'll try to hit him again.
Those two are good.
Plus eight melee.
Nine, 17.
Yeah, I unfortunately don't have anything silver.
We have the necklaces technically.
She threw a few.
I'm assuming we may all have a necklace.
Sure.
We're just going to have to burn actions like flint it onto the weapon or something.
I'm just like...
It's going to be a while.
It's going to be...
Well, can't you, like, crush metals and stuff?
Can't you, like... You're a doer's pit.
Yeah, you're a doer's pit.
You can grind it up.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That takes time.
Yeah, yeah, probably.
That's a lot of battle.
Generous amount of time.
That's, yeah, six rounds.
Four seconds max.
Crush a whole necklace.
I can't do that anymore, so...
Um, are you wild chained?
No.
Oh, gotcha.
Plus I only have one attack, wild chained anyway.
You hit the flame blade, but you also multi-attack your top, right?
Yeah, but I still have flame blade up.
Well, so you can do either.
You can either do the fire damage or the multi-attack going forward on that.
Oh, okay.
Because since they're like interchangeable damage-wise, there wasn't a benefit of doing one, but I'm not going to say you can do a multi-attack with fire damage.
So one or the other, you get the versatility of that.
Gotcha.
Yeah, no, I'm just me.
Calla.
I'm going to use my bonus action.
Roll to save for the fear.
Oh.
That's a huge number.
Yeah, I mean it's tough.
18, I have plus zero, so.
Bonus action.
One to ten.
This object blasts.
That's it, first one's a three, it's gonna miss.
Second one is gonna also miss at a five.
I'll run forward and try to hit it with a knife player.
Yep.
That's gonna maybe hit at 21.
Nice.
That's terrible.
Sorry, we're swinging some damage there.
That's 13, no, 12 plus 3, 15.
Okay.
That's all I can do now.
I'm now right up next to him because I ran forward to him.
Start of his turn.
See that slash sort of catches up and the fur replaces.
A little bit of blood smear, but it seems to heal still.
Eight will roll.
No, I didn't.
But I don't think I would have rolled.
It's a crit?
No.
Good looking out.
It will do a slash on both of you.
It's not feeling super threatened in the moment.
What?
Not feeling threatened?
A miss on Zariel.
Okay.
18.
Mitsu beats it, but hits a decoy.
Perfect.
End of its turn, it'll do two legendary actions to bite.
It was facing this way at the end of its turn.
It will bite you.
21.
It's another... Nice.
Fantastic.
After that, Leopold.
So you get to fucking hit everyone.
Um...
No, you should throw silver coins.
Yeah, that's what I was going to catapult.
I have one.
Does it have to be a stone?
Magic stone has to be a stone, but he has catapult also.
Catapult those coins, dude.
I'm going to, let's say, I'm going to shotgun him.
At level two, this is my only remaining spell slot, I'm gonna just start hucking silver coins down my gullet.
Let's see, how much silver do I have?
I had a 50, I'll send 10 down.
And you'll just kind of .
Bring in 10 silver pieces, we'll go buckshot towards him.
I think it is a, yeah, let me read it.
It's a dex save 16.
Second level.
So it fails.
object strikes the target stops moving when the object strikes something it's 3d8 bludgeoning damage oh at higher levels so 48 48 because it was second level i need some more gates yeah nice
Uh, 10... Oh, shit.
15.
But, uh...
He doesn't heal for 20.
Because I hit him with something silver.
Now it won't heal at all.
Because it took silver.
Forever.
Forever, yeah.
I'm sure that's how we're...
It'll never stop for one round.
I do not have the ability to do that again, so... Oh, no.
Um...
That was my attack.
For my bonus action, I will animate some magic stones.
And that's my turn.
At the end of your turn, it will use its last legendary action and take a swipe at you.
26 to hit.
Is even rolling these at this advantage?
The wolf.
I'm gonna roll for my fear too.
Go ahead.
You take 16 points of slashing damage and give me a con saving throw.
I remember being stuck in a position like this, so I was playing Bard, and my whole set was like 0.
Yeah, that's what mine's like.
18 is like a minus 1 or a 0.
18 will take half damage, so that's 22, half of 11 to grind.
I'm so frightened.
I don't know.
I don't want to fight.
That's fairly fitting for a level.
End of the round, nobody can change on green, so nothing happens.
Start of it is Zariel.
Alright, I might swap, um...
Dex 15.
I'm going to draw a little Spiritfire.
First level.
No spell we could possibly cast is going to be above 30.
19 plus 3.
Alright.
Nothing happens.
And I don't have any more objections.
Yeah.
Alright.
Yep, that's it.
Was that, like, Pokemon Trainer?
Death Metal?
That was also the Legend of Zelda one.
Oh, that was Zelda, okay.
Alright, yeah, that's all I got.
Okay.
To your damage, you did your thing.
Up next is Kaladin.
How far down the hole are you still?
You've only made it 25 feet.
Oh, well, I had movement, right?
Yes, you kind of moved.
So I'll move up to the ledge, but depending on how much did I have?
Would have been half movement to get up, so 30 feet, so I'm letting you get up to the top.
Okay.
I'm just going to cling to the very top edge.
I'm not going to pop over and stand, so that way I'm still isolated from the wolf.
Perfect.
All I can do is swing one time.
You can swing and then also bonus action do that thing.
I know, that's with disadvantage.
Disadvantage is better than nothing.
It is.
All right, yeah, I'm gonna do my first just weapon attack with Blight Splitter.
And that's a 14 hit?
14 misses?
Oh, advantage, yeah, that's good.
That's hard.
A little bonus action misty step for the last time.
Just far enough away again just to be able to do this after it blasts.
I'm just rolling both dice for each hit.
One's gonna hit, one's gonna miss.
17 plus seven hits.
11 misses.
That'll be seven force damage.
Start of its turn.
Does not heal.
It will see if it gets its fight back.
It does.
Just what we need.
Spin around clumsily on this, and it'll take its two attacks on you.
Good luck.
Yeah.
Gonna need it.
First one is 14 to hit.
Nope.
Second one.
Natural 20.
What's it at?
Going down.
29.
Jeez.
Give me a con save.
That's low rolls, though.
4, 7, 14, 22.
Double.
44.
Okay, so you take that was 11 plus 5 so 16 times 2 Cool 32 on the slashing.
Yeah, and you take only 7 points of necrotic damage Yeah, I'm doing totally fine
I'm glad.
No problems.
Apple.
You're still smiling?
I'm doing good.
I got no problems.
At the end of its turn, it'll use two legendary actions and bite you.
Me?
Yes.
No.
We're friends.
I'm cursed.
Natural 20.
Oh my god.
This is... That does hit.
This is nasty.
That does hit.
Okay.
I'm gonna use luck.
Give me another... Do you have luck?
19.
19, you pass.
You take half damage.
It's just still doubled.
As long as you don't roll 16, I'll be fine.
Lost when I was 32.
Doubled.
I'm going to be all right.
I think I'll be fine.
You're not going to die, right?
Nah.
I got plot armor.
What's funny is that I have Meridivify, and I'm the only one that can bring people up if they actually die-die.
So, that's unfortunate.
I am unconscious.
Yeah.
I'm not all the way.
Oh, it's not double what your total was.
Okay.
Yeah.
Your hit points.
Oh, that's it.
Oh, that's close.
That was technically it's 86, which would have been doubled, but you passed.
So it's just, so I would have been dead.
You would have been dead.
Just immediately dead.
Yeah.
Uh, Leopold, you're up.
I'm rolling.
No, I can't move any closer.
Is there a way I could, you know, is this technically closer?
I think what I'll do is I'll spin around and hit him with what I got.
Okay.
I'm going to create a cantrip or a bonfire right underneath him.
with create bonfire.
Bonfire on the ground.
Yeah.
16.
That's a silver bonfire, right?
It's a silver bonfire, yeah.
18 plus 3.
This one is dead.
But it's just going to hang.
Is that a half?
I guess it's a tantrum.
Must succeed a dex save throw or take 1d8 fire damage.
Must also make a saving throw when it moves into the bonfire for the first time or ends its turn there.
So that's my action.
For bonus action, I will do magic stone.
And I'll stone.
I'm fucking incredibly frightened right now.
So that's plus nine, so 21.
And magic stone is D6 plus five.
Seven damage.
I don't know where we're going to run.
Oh, the hole he can't fit.
Yeah, the one place he can't go.
I can't run towards him.
You've got to make your save.
Oh, yeah.
I guess speaking of...
Okay, are we six rounds in?
What are we at, five?
We're at nine.
Nine, oh my gosh.
I rolled that nine five.
Nailed everyone.
Sorry, you're at the start of the round.
Okay, so let's see.
I'm going to roll.
I'm gonna use this nice rose dice.
It's been good to me.
Right here.
It's not a one.
They've been good to you.
It's a die.
Dying quickly.
Kaladin, your turn.
This reminds me of one of my favorite memes, which is like when your DM says, roll a D8, roll another D8, now roll another D8, I pick a name.
Alright, great, great, great.
Just pick a name.
What's a name that you like?
That's great.
My other one is...
When your DM says 28, and you're like, damage?
And I'm like, to hit.
Yeah, I think I'll do two of this.
I'll do a melee attack.
I can't even get to you.
No, I don't think so.
Maybe you could, like, Vine Whip Swing.
Yeah, do a Tarzan.
It's huge, you could get underneath it.
I'm gonna go past the bonfire.
Step over it.
Although it would be better to not all three of us die.
I can't get past it anyway, so I'm fucking toast.
I can bring you up, but it's just going to bring us right back down.
Okay, am I within 30 feet?
Mm-hmm.
And I can run under him?
Well, I mean, make any dexterity or athletic checks.
Oh, 30 feet next to Zario?
Yeah, it's 30 feet within Zario.
No, he's 60.
Yes, I can't.
Oh, you have to dash, huh?
Yeah.
I'll do the two blasts, nat 21 hits.
Double that damage.
14.
And then I'll swing again with light splitter.
How many specials do you guys pick for a level?
Like five or six.
Ah man, more than that.
Yeah.
Probably at least seven.
It's been a while.
Leveled up two seconds ago.
I think it was.
I checked the chat.
It was.
Oh, it's not with the damage.
You're down.
You're just dead.
Can we move you forward?
We need an inside melee.
That's okay.
That's a 20, dirty 20 to hit.
Hits.
Nice.
This will be the first time you guys broke 100 damage on it.
Like as in it has 100 health?
I was going to say, that means it's down.
Because it has exactly 100.
Another six radiant.
That's my whole turn.
I'm just screaming at it.
Start its turn.
It'll heal.
Could I, could I have, okay, no, I'll have to use an action.
It also starts its turn on the fire, correct?
Yep.
So it'll make a dex save.
16.
That's with advantage, that's a 14, that's a fail.
Alright.
Ooh, at least it takes some of that.
What's the damage?
Uh, it is, uh, a little bit of disadvantage on the next one.
Oh, oh, nice, 2d8.
Nice.
Uh, but it'll spin.
We'll see if it gets its bite.
Oh, here's the other one.
Six.
So yeah, two spits appear and he just starts rotating.
It will not claw you.
It can bite or claw on that round, so it'll take its bite on you.
After its turn though, it will claw at you.
Misses.
That is Leopold.
Back to me.
Jeez, can't do anything.
Can you give yourself advantage in any way?
Can you do anything to help your skills?
To beat the whiz saving throw?
Yeah, yeah.
Can you do anything?
Like ability score?
Not ability score.
I don't have any more spells.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Well, there's that.
But even if I could, none of these necessarily would give me advantage.
Oh, dear.
Oh, dear, dear.
We have to call pretty soon, too.
We might end this mid-battle.
Yeah, I gotta go.
I will cast Firebolt.
I just can't trip.
Actually, well, I'll call forth Steel Defender.
Okay.
Who won't be frightened, correct?
Will not.
Cool.
And set him forth to attack.
How far away can you summon him?
I think it comes off of me, but 45 feet of movement.
My only thought was that you could put him over here and then you'd give him advantage.
Oh.
You can keep it into combat.
And then I'll use a bonus action to do Magic Stone.
Okay.
Which is 20 to hit.
20 hits.
And then 1d6 plus 5.
6 damage.
ripping it into him and then the uh still defender will be come on uh plus nine to hit i got a good feeling about this yeah that's gonna be a uh 11 that was a good feeling but good roll for this one
For what one?
Oh, oh, oh.
For the... Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on.
All the good energy.
How's a 10?
A 10?
Normally a 10's fantastic.
It's pretty even.
And this, not so great.
I've rolled a 17.
That's the highest so far.
...in range.
Started around Zariel.
Oh, shit.
Before you make your save, you, um, are finding yourself in that weird dream space again where it's like a memory but you're not totally sure.
Uh, you remember...
when you first woke up and you're having a memory of this person reading the things that you can do.
And he looks down and just like, elven ears pointing back and he's got this very high faith presence of importance and he goes, needs to be resilient.
I need it to be there when I need it.
And you have the option
change your form to your true form, you can pop up.
Your new... Yeah, we're talking like new where form is what I'm assuming.
I'm talking... Oh, even better.
Backstory stuff.
I think that although normally Zariel is an existentialist, I think he's very afraid of death, so he's...
Two hour forges.
The body soup he was in.
Basically, it just looks like...
I can't remember the movies because I only watched it that one time.
Ultron.
Like the robot in Age of Ultron.
Yeah, just like that, but just bigger.
I stand up out of my bodysuit shell, and then I just kind of get a little bit wider and a little bit bigger, and there's like the spaces just kind of separate out.
Like that.
And yeah, there's like this like faintish like purplish greenish hue glow that's just emanating from all the cracks and, you know, stuff.
Blazend on his chest is a big Z.
Interesting.
Zorro is my real name.
So your human skin is shedded.
Full metal iron torch.
Just bald.
I want to have iron hair.
You have iron hair?
No.
Fake hair.
So yeah.
What does that mean for me?
Give yourself the effects of a short rest.
So roll some hit dice.
There we go.
Some magic afoot.
When we started the story, and you said you were Warforged, she wanted to change it.
I was like, don't just give up on being a Warforged.
That's fine.
Let's see if I can do this.
All right, short rest.
There's more of us than you would happen to imagine though.
All right, so I got 43 back on a thing.
Let's see.
Alright, so I have my action.
I have both my forms.
So I'm going to do a... Let's check one thing.
Alright, I'm going to turn into a giant bubble constrictor.
And I'm going to attack with a...
constrict attack.
Is this a metal boa constrictor?
So 26.
It's kind of up to him.
I see.
Do your animals take the... Yeah, yeah.
Instead of like morphing, I just like... Yeah, I like that.
So that's going to be...
The bear still has a hat.
Can I have like silver?
You don't know what metal type I am.
We didn't discuss it before.
That's going to be 2d8 plus 4, and then I need a dc.
Actually, I think you're just grappled if I hit, and then you have to roll to escape.
So that's going to be 2d8 plus 4.
How do I not have a d8?
Oh, I'm just freaked out.
7, 12, 16 bludgeoning damage.
as I constrict, and then he is grappled.
Okay.
And it's your turn as Kaladin.
Can I do, like, an object manipulation?
Can I wrap the necklace around my sword and then take an attack?
Yeah.
Me coming back might not be a cue for us to try to kill this thing.
It might be a cue for us to leave.
I can't run.
That's why I constricted it.
Just to try to hold it still.
I guess the question is, is this technically moving closer if I parallel it?
I have to close the distance?
What if you maintain the same radius like that?
Just climb up the wall?
And then went around.
Just go into one of these little tunnels.
And he had no definitive answer there.
Oh, was it?
For what?
Oh, if you can't?
No, if he can run in that direction.
He can't.
He doesn't have space.
I can't.
And I can't go underneath.
Well, I guess if I went underneath, that would be... And he's... Technically moving away from it.
It would.
You're grappling him.
What does that give him?
Disadvantage on... Just movement zero until he breaks it.
Disadvantage on attacks that are creatures that are not him.
Not me.
So technically disadvantage on anything but me, so it's not hitting you.
And then it can't, like, chase after anybody or go anywhere.
So it doesn't have a reaction.
It couldn't take a reactionary.
Well, it could, but it would be disadvantage.
Yeah.
You could push it down the ground, and then the bolt could run by.
That's a good call.
Get up there and shove it.
Yeah.
I'm new in town.
Like when you say push it down into the pit, you mean?
Yeah, I want to use Thunder Wave, my last level 2 spell slot, but it still has advantage against that save.
You want to try it anyway?
Could we do something where I'm wrapped around its legs to try to ice cooler it?
That's something else.
No, that's it.
That's the only way I can force it.
I've got my own strength, which is...
Thunder wave a save?
Thunder wave is a save.
Okay, what kind of save is it?
Oh, what save is it?
Con.
It's got banish.
But why the...
It's already got it.
Because it spells underneath.
But if Kaladin takes a stress point... Take a stress point and a heartbeat.
I want to live for the greater good.
This is evocation, so can I just blast it out of Zariel's grip?
You can choose to push Zariel away by you agree to take in this extra bit of force.
You feel like that pulse of the core that had sort of like gone into your body and was just sort of resonating in there.
It sort of channels out of your hands as you cast this much bigger spell than you anticipated and it throws Zariel past onto this.
The Steel Defender back.
You get thrown back and this entire walk
topples down to the side as it falls 60 feet.
Go ahead and roll double damage.
Sweet.
Which will take a fifth stress point.
So it'll be 3d8 for 1, 5, and 13 total.
That's Force or is that Thunder?
Nice Thunder damage.
Nice.
Oh, that wasn't double, though.
Did you double that number?
No.
There you go.
Another 14.
Okay.
We'll figure out what happens to you later.
And I'll use my full movement to not get close enough to the wall to get that opportunity to attack.
Skirting the edge.
Right up to the edge.
And then on its turn, it falls 60 feet.
It'll take 5d6 damage.
yeah that's the most damage we've done to it 17 21 I did it I had it a bunch of times it just heals everything I did it for I was gonna say that's 21 damage so it really only took one damage I was gonna say one hit point for the whole battle I mean that's pretty good yeah but then it heals on its turn but well you hit it too it is 60 feet down and the bonfire fell with it right yeah it's burning it already has the disadvantage because it hasn't taken a strike since then um
This cow's going to get it.
Craig's going to be so confused.
What fucking cow?
It's a transforming werewolf.
Oscillating between cow and wolf.
Werecow?
Werecow.
It's a wool vine.
I'm going to say it'll have to use its full action to get up.
Give me a luck check.
11 or higher.
It goes after Zariel, not getting close to Leopold.
Who wants it?
Two.
It starts to climb up this wall.
But it only has 60 feet normally, so 30 feet.
It gets 30 feet up the wall, climbing, scraping, going down a little bit.
Leopold, it is your turn.
So I can't cross over towards Zariel there.
All right, jump back into the fog, run all the way over here, and run up this side.
Yeah, that would be cool.
If I was still a monk, I could probably just casually do that.
We've had to kill your character before.
We'll do it again.
Do, do.
Would Leopold really want to get past finally?
I mean, he's terrified.
He's terrified of this creature.
Surely it's one minute.
Is it just the whole time?
Yeah.
If you take another stress point, you can get by.
I'm going to try... Let's see.
Frost doesn't create difficult drain or make it slippery.
It just does cold damage.
Okay.
um sure yeah so for my action i'll do a fireball okay um but i guess am i just making it pass or am i dispelling the frightened status which would you want to do how well how would you want to approach it
Would Leopold's mind be thinking, like, fleeing mentality, if I just need to get by?
Or would he be like, I need to end this hold on me?
Yeah, so I think that, you know, over the few weeks he's been in the Legionnaire, he's evolved to...
Not to be terribly afraid of battles, but still realizes that maybe he's a bit of a coward.
So in his brain, he's kind of taking these in and realizing that maybe he needs to get over this.
He needs to, for the sake of his friends and his companions, break the hold the creature has on him.
He'll still take the stress point.
could happen with your armor.
But when you make the decision of how you want to end it, you see you have like a glow that comes from like your chest piece that sends out like a wave through your whole suit of armor and it ends the effect of fear.
Do I also hit the stress point?
No.
You're taking your true form.
You're just showing your colors now.
You're just no longer human.
Okay, so that gives me four stress points, correct?
Yeah.
It's four.
I was going to say, yeah.
Stress points.
Okay, so then that effect ends.
So then I don't have disadvantage on the attack, which is convenient.
So it's a flat roll.
18 to hit.
That was a D12.
Oh, fuck.
You might get higher.
As it is, it misses.
16, yeah, still, that would hit, right?
And then that's 2d10.
Yeah, I know.
And that's a d10 too.
Is that a one?
And disadvantage.
But then with a bonus action, I will do a stone.
18 to hit.
18 misses.
Misses.
And then I will finally, with my fear broken, I have 30 feet of movement, so yeah, I'll move right up here to... That's Kaladin, right?
Mm-hmm.
At the start of the round, you are close to the wall.
Give me a dex saving throw.
All right.
15?
15 makes it.
I think I've already been bit.
Although this would be damage.
Sorry, you're up at the start of the round.
This is no longer a viable pass.
So I have to jump.
If you can jump 60 feet.
No, I meant this way.
Yes, you could go that way.
Snakes can't really jump, can they?
No, but they're pretty good at climbing walls and stuff if there's texture.
If I was a giant elf, could I carry somebody?
Yeah.
I'm going to drop this form as a bonus action.
As an action, I'm going to become a giant elf.
Could a giant elf fit through the cage?
It's a midget giant elf.
You can't carry somebody.
So it's a giant elf, but it's small.
It's a small giant elf.
All the stats of a giant elf, but it's really tiny.
It's a contradiction.
a snake and i'll your movement spew is a snake it's the same oh really it's a fast snake i'm a giant snake yeah the entrance if you can go 60 feet yeah yeah okay um i guess i'll go to the entrance and wait hang out slowly around yeah i'll you know eat some spiders or something do i do anyone
Kaladin, it's your turn.
I'll use my bonus action to cast the Sophrac Blast, and I'm going to be trying to blast the rock where it's holding.
Neither of them can.
That's why I'm trying to do that.
I'll use my action and movement to run as far as I can.
How long is the...
I guess that's probably a concentration thing, isn't it?
Yeah.
I don't know if I'm concentrated on anything else.
It started its turn.
Oh, I did Fogglot.
It did not take silver damage, did it?
No.
I think it's only taken silver damage once.
I think you got it for two of those.
Oh, did I?
and it'll take it to a closet you as you're trying to run by maybe it is the steel defenders within five foot right yes so it will impose disadvantage on that strike 18 18 plus 9 27. jesus christ you take 10 slashing with give me a con save
Uh, 12.
You take 17 points of necrotic damage.
I'm down.
Well, and plus 10, right?
No.
Yeah, well.
Oh, plus the 10 other damage.
Yeah, so, I'm down.
That's rough with disadvantage.
Roll two 18s.
Your steel defender?
On my attack?
Yeah.
Can it?
It'll take its other attack on your steel defender.
Okay.
Does it have disadvantage?
No, because I think I can only impose disadvantage on attacks against others.
That's dirty 20 to hit.
Yeah, that hits.
Eight damage.
Is it immune to anything?
Poison.
Okay.
Con saving throw then?
Plus five on the con.
uh so that would be 23. take seven points of damage instead yeah okay started your turn give me a death saving throw can his steel defender interact with him he can't yes uh six fail fail your steel defender now goes um so yeah steel defender is not necessarily within
attack of opportunity reaches.
Not until it leaves its face.
Right.
So, Steel Defender will come to my aid and administer one of my healing syringes.
Okay.
Which is a regular health potion?
Mm-hmm.
So, what's that like?
You just bought a greater.
Ah, yeah, yeah.
So, well, I guess I could just have it administer whatever it is I want it to, right?
Mm-hmm.
44 plus 4?
Yep, I'll do that.
We've got one, two, three, four, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, fifteen.
And you were up, but it's not your turn.
And then your still defender can attempt to carry you at half speed.
Oh, okay.
But it will take an attack of opportunity.
The defender or me?
The defender.
Yeah, okay.
Let's go ahead and do that.
Yeah, I don't think you would move on if you're involuntarily taking an attack of combat.
It hits it.
Does four plus five, nine plus a con saving throw.
10, 18, necrotic halved, or not halved, depending on the con save.
Con is plus 5, so 19 on the con save.
So that's saved, so 9, 9.
So what's the total damage?
18.
Yes, 9 and 9.
Two little hit points left.
That's okay.
As long as there's a barrier.
Let's see.
That's convenient that I didn't have to take that because I would have been dead.
This is the first time we've actually had to flee.
I didn't think we'd have to do that.
Yeah, maybe we just need to come back with some silver.
Just be ready for that component of it.
I was so missing.
Even just chill touching it because that's got a 120-foot radius.
I'll do it.
Oh, yeah.
That's a cantrip.
I'll do a healing word as a bonus action.
I'll do a third level.
So that's a 3d4 plus 4.
I'll do 1 if you do 2.
3d4.
You want me to do 2d4?
2d4s.
I'll roll 1, 2.
4.
So 6, so 10.
You get another 10 healing.
Very nice.
And then I'm just going to chill by the door as a snake.
Okay.
I'll hold an action.
Callie?
I'll, again, try to both miss.
Doesn't matter.
I'll run.
Get out of there.
I haven't rolled over a ten in a hot second.
To the entrance.
You can jump.
Give me an athletics check.
I'm going to wriggle my tail out.
You can give him assistance.
Grab on.
Give a Tarzan slide down a log.
Or just a much easier DC.
It's a DC 10.
So yeah, you jump, catch onto the snake body, climb up into the hole.
That would be great if you just missed that and fell 60 feet down.
Whoa!
Jesus.
And you're still down, huh?
No, I'm back up.
Steel Defender.
I meant you're still down.
It'll take...
It is still prone, yes.
Oh, yeah, I guess I have to stand up.
It's fight attack on the Steel Defender.
It misses.
That's seven on that one.
That's great.
Steel Defender has the AC of 15.
Why did it roll?
Oh, okay, cool.
Is that good, though?
Because if you miss on the bite...
So, Steel Defender's carrying me.
Yeah, it's turn is over.
But I guess it goes after mine.
Legendary action.
It'll take a swipe at the Steel Defender.
8 plus 9, 17.
2d8, 17.
10 plus 5, 15 plus, give me a con save.
Add things obliterated.
Add two hit points.
Leaves you, sort of like dunks you forward into a running position as it gets destroyed because it only lives to serve you.
Okay.
Your turn.
Yeah, so I'm going to dash and I'm going to move 60 feet.
As far as I can get.
Okay.
Top of the round is Dario.
Let's see here.
I think I'm going to just run.
Yeah, I think I'm just going to dash.
What's your health looking like?
25.
Better than it was.
I'll give you another third level healing word.
So that's 3d4 plus 4, so give me another 2d4.
It's a 3.
4, yeah, 8.
Damn.
11, so 15.
15.
15?
Nice.
Yeah, that's pretty good.
That'll give me enough to get my ass eaten a few times.
And then I'll action and movement forward 60 feet.
Okay, you're out of there.
The thought of you're going to have to bury this hole on your way out or get mauled or just keep hauling acid to get out of here because you'll be followed does resonate, but Kaladin's up next.
I'm going to do the same thing.
I'll try to hit it with two of the blasts.
And you're aiming for where its feet are at the stone.
The ledge.
It's still right at the ledge, correct.
It's eight.
Eleven.
Fifteen.
We'll say it drops a little bit.
It'll have to use movement to get on top of it and it probably won't reach him.
And then do you leave?
I'll move twenty, thirty feet down the tunnel.
It's turned heels again.
It is.
Back to full health.
So it's within attack of opportunity?
Okay.
I'm gonna try and run up here, but can I take my time and maybe try and sidestep this and not necessarily try a big rope jump?
Yeah, you've got more than enough movement.
Even at half speed, you get in the hole.
So that way I don't have to roll to miss that ledge.
You get in.
I'm going to use my action to dash.
Dash?
You guys want to try to blow up the hole or something?
Yeah, I was thinking once I can see that they're both inside, I want to try to do a thing where I rotate my body and lift and create a space for them to pass me.
And I want to just really, really stretch out the opening.
and then just like drop and move forward and try to get it to collapse yeah so maybe like a constrict attack or what is like your highest thing your highest role you can make my highest role what does that mean what's your best modifier oh uh it's gonna be wisdom that's gonna be uh
Yeah, my wisdom is a 18, so it'll be a plus 4.
Okay, so go ahead and make it like a wisdom-based attack, so plus 7 to the d20 roll.
Okay.
17.
Yes, so that succeeds.
All right, so I'll be stopped up ahead.
Stands your body out, drops in, moves forward.
Great thing about being a serpent is you can dig, so even as the dirt's falling on you, you're still moving.
And we'll stop it right there.
As you guys are now on the run.
That was ill-prepared.
Love it when a plan comes in.
Immensely ill-prepared.
You guys just went right in.
I love, I really do love the fact that the one thing that we got as advice was, hey, take silver.
And we went, we'll just, we'll take your next.
You said, yeah, give me your stuff and we're going to go buy other things.
Yeah.
I'm really glad I bought those three health potions and no... And I'm glad I bought that ring that I'm not even using.
recoup will be where his apps would still make sense oh dear we should have brought some silver with us